"I'll say yon grey
is not the morning's eye
"'tis but the pale
reflect of Cynthia's brow
"nor that is not the lark
"whose notes do beat
"the vaulty heavens
so high above our heads.
"I have more care to stay
than will to go.
Come, Death. And welcome."
Yes! He nailed it!
Malcolm, that was wonderful!
So sensitive
and full of passion.
It was just beautiful.
Before you say anything
just remember
we're best friends.
So that wheelchair
isn't going to stop
me from kicking your ass.
Bring it on, Homeo.
* Yes, no, maybe *
* I don't know *
* Can you repeat the question? *
* You're not the boss of me now *
* And you're not so big *
* Life is unfair. **
Lois: What do you mean
what happens when you die?
You're dead.
That's it.
Now, honey,
that's not quite true.
Actually, son, after death
your body undergoes
a fascinating series of changes.
First it bloats up like a balloon
then shrivels like a raisin.
Then tiny microbes
you can't even see,
but are on you right now
start to devour your flesh
and return all the elements
in your body back to the soil.
Now, some people will tell you
that your hair keeps growing,
but that's... that's a myth.
It's actually
your head that shrinks.
Now go get ready
for Aunt Helen's funeral.
Julie, listen, I'm sorry
I'm canceling out so late.
That's okay.
I mean, it's a funeral.
So, were you close with your aunt?
No, but I guess my mom was.
She keeps saying
how important this is.
Anyway, I'm really sorry.
Especially since you're stuck
with the extra ticket.
Well, that's okay.
Maybe I'll askJimmy to go.
Who's Jimmy?
Jimmy Westcott.
He plays football.
Bye.
Oh, yeah. Life's fair.
Did you call that girl?
Yes, I called her and told her
I couldn't go to the concert
and now she's probably
going to invite someone else.
Well, Malcolm, I'm sorry
that my mother's sister...
the woman who took care of me
every day after school...
had to die and inconvenience
your social life.
She does it on purpose.
I could have made up a million
different escape plans
but now my brain
is filled with mom guilt.
Who's this?
How should I know.
Hal?
Beats me.
Dewey...
is this a friend of yours?
Uh-huh.
Who is he?
I don't know.
What's your name, son?
(inaudible)
Did he say Greg?
I thought he said Craig.
His name is Egg.
Egg?
I named him.
Well, you can't keep him.
He needs to go home, okay?
Okay.
This stinks.
Whether it's a wedding,
funeral or court date
these family gatherings
are always the same.
I can't wait till I get zits.
At least then I can fight back.
Hal, you have to get ready.
Why are you still messing around
with those record albums?
I thought I was going
to spend today in the garage
listening to them
on my quadraphonic
but now that we're going
to the funeral
I have to reseal the shrink wrap.
Hal!
I have to get my speech ready.
Honey, you know
you don't have to talk
at every funeral we go to.
I wish that were true.
You see how people look to me
when they ask if somebody has
a few words to say?
They're not looking to you
they're looking at you.
To, at... what's the difference?
(phone ringing)
Hello.
Hey, Mom, I'm just warning you
someone claiming to be
the Commandant might call you.
It's this guy down the hall.
Play along and pretend
you believe him.
He's totally harmless.
I can't talk to you right now.
We're on our way
to Aunt Helen's funeral.
Aunt Helen died?
Well, I sure hope so.
We're going to her funeral.
Well, when did she die?
Mom, why didn't anybody tell me?
We didn't want to have
to worry you over nothing.
Nothing? She's dead.
How's Uncle Fred taking it?
I don't think he's thought
too much about it.
He died two months ago.
What?!
Francis, I'm sorry.
I really have to go.
Here, talk to your brother.
Mom? Hello?
All right, let's see it.
I can't breathe.
Fine.
You know the drill.
Upgrade.
See? Problem solved.
Hello?
Oh.
Okay, well, you can wear
one of the suits that
Uncle Fred left you.
Aw, Mom, a dead suit?
Cool. A dead suit.
Dewey, why don't you help
your little friend find his way out?
Dewey: I did.
He keeps coming back.
This thing's an open casket, right?
I think so. Why?
Because I'm going to stash
this with Aunt Helen.
What is that?
It's a Mighty Man.
Mom and Dad had it in their closet
for some reason.
It's Dewey's birthday next week.
This is his present.
Oh.
What'd you do to it?
I stomped on it.
Why would you do that?
Look, I don't know why
I do the things I do.
I just know I don't
want to get caught.
That's why Aunt Helen
is getting a new friend.
You're going to bury
that with her?
You are so dead.
Hey, I watch lawyer shows.
Mom will think I did it
but she can't prove it
without this.
It's in the Constitution...
No evidence, no conviction.
E pluribus unum.
(chuckling):
Oh, yeah.
Hi, honey.
I finally found my joke cards.
They were behind the water heater.
- Really?
- Hey, how's this?
"A priest, a rabbi
and Uncle Fred are..."
Aunt Helen.
"Are playing golf
with Saint Peter."
Hal, please.
Have you seen my pun file?
It's in a box marked
"laughter thoughts."
Laughter thoughts?
How did she die?
Cats ate her face.
Dewey, I think you're confused.
I'm asking about Aunt Helen.
Cats ate her face.
Put Mom or Dad on the phone.
Hello?
Dad, what happened to Aunt Helen?
Cats ate her face. Dewey
knows more about it than I do.
Mom, I hate wearing
Reese's hand-me-downs.
Look at this.
Jelly in the pockets,
the fly's broken
and it smells like wet dog.
Well, you should be glad
he only wore it once.
You know, I'm trying
to be there for Mom
but the annoyances are starting
to outweigh the guilt.
I'm this close to sneaking
out of the whole thing.
Well, I suppose you're
entitled to complain.
After all,
it's only my Aunt Helen.
What is she, a mind reader?
And then there were
ants on her bones
and the police came.
Dad, listen...
can you think of anything
that rhymes with cadaver?
How long is this
funeral going to take?
Including traveling time?
All day.
(sighs)
I know, I know.
But it will
make your mom happy.
Mom really loved Aunt Helen, huh?
Oh, God, no.
Your mom hated her.
What? She hated her?
Everyone did.
Horrible woman.
I used to have
to forbid her from
calling here 'cause
she always made your mom cry.
I can't believe Mom
tricked me like that.
I'll tell you one thing...
I now consider myself totally free
to ditch this funeral.
I got to callJulie.
Hello?
Malcolm!
Thank God,
somebody I can talk to.
Sorry, I have to make a call.
(dial tone)
So, your aunt's... not dead?
No. It turned out to be
one of those comas
where they think you're dead
and they put you
on the embalmer's table
and you wake up
at the last second.
It was a close call.
Uh, okay.
I guess we'll pick you up at 2:00.
Great.
I figure I'll commit to it first
and come up with a plan later.
I always think better
under pressure...
or is it when
I'm not under pressure?
Oh, well.
Too late now.
I'm ready to go.
Yeah. Hey!
You're taking a backpack
to the funeral?
My back gets cold.
Fair enough.
Lois:
Look, Francis
I guess I get scattered.
You know, sometimes
I forget what I told you
and you're not here so...
I'm not there
because you sent me away.
I swear, I'm not even
a part of this family anymore.
Francis, it's very important
that you understand
that is not true
but I don't have time right now.
I understand.
It's not like it's a matter
of life and death.
Oh, wait, it is!
Anyone else die in the last
five minutes
I should know about?
You wanna know everything
that's been happening?
Your father mowed the lawn
Reese polished off all the cereal
and I dropped
a frying pan on my foot
and I got a big black toe.
You want me to send a picture?
Egg! Cut it out!
What is Egg?
Oh, he's a new boy in the house.
What?!
Okay, it'll only hurt
for a second
and I'll get out of the funeral.
I can tellJulie
a really cool story
about how I got my black eye.
Aw, I'm so gutless.
Why are you taking so long?
Let's go.
Reese, listen.
I know it sounds crazy
but I need you to hit me.
(groans)
You idiot!
In the eye!
And leave a mark for Mom to see?
Forget it.
No bruises, no evidence...
no crime.
I guess we move on
to plan "B:" lying.
What book report?
I just remembered.
I have a big book report
due tomorrow
and I haven't even
started reading it.
Standard technique...
You volunteer a small crime
to distract them
from looking for the big one.
So, what's the report on?
A Tale of Two Cities.
- Oh, how many words?
- 750.
Was that on your
assignment sheet?
- No, it's an addendum.
- When did you get that?
Thursday.
I didn't bring it home.
That's why I forgot
to do the assignment.
Ooh, nice one.
Well, I suppose
if it's school work...
That's the mislead.
Wait for the reverse.
A Tale of Two Cities.
Who's that by?
Charles Dickens.
Oh, I thought it was Victor Hugo.
No, it's Dickens.
Is that the one
with Jean Valjean?
That's Les Miserables.
No, no.
Isn't A Tale of Two Cities
the one with Jean Valjean,
where he's says
"It's a far, far
better thing I do..."
right before he steals
a loaf of bread?
No. Sidney Carton says that
right before they behead him.
I thought you hadn't read it.
What?
No. I said I hadn't written it.
And when is it due?
Tomorrow, I told you.
- On Les Miserables?
- Yes. No!
- A Tale of Two Cities.
- Which you haven't read.
- Right.
- But you just said you did.
No, l-I said I didn't,
and then you said...
it was Thursday, and...
Look, I just don't want to go
to this stupid funeral.
There's no reason for me to go
and I want to go
to the concert with Julie!
Let's go!
I'll be waiting in the car.
Malcolm
I am ashamed of you...
Wanting to deny
your poor Aunt Helen her due.
No, that won't work on me
because I know
you didn't love Aunt Helen.
You hated her!
'Course I did. What does that
have to do with anything?
What?
Malcolm,
this isn't about love.
It's about family.
We have a duty to this family
and we are darn well
going to do it.
But why?
It's not fair.
You can't just stick the word
"family" in front of something
and turn everyone
else into slaves.
It makes no sense.
No one liked this woman
so why do we have
to pretend like we did now?
What good will it do anybody?
Hal?
I got nothing.
I could really use
some support here.
Excuse me?
I am being
incredibly supportive.
I'm giving up my entire day
for this-this thing
and you don't hear me
complaining.
Hal, it was a bunch
of old record albums.
You're not giving up
something important.
Well, they're important to me.
You-You people.
I can't believe you.
I asked you to do
one thing that...
You're not asking:
You're ordering.
Lois:
After all I do
for this family.
I cook, I clean,
I spackle, I plunge
and none of it means anything
to any of you people
and the one time
I ask you for something...
something that I shouldn't even
have to ask you for...
and all I get are complaints!
Well, what about me, hmm?
You think I want to be
cleaning out the gutters
when I could be surfing
the beaches of Europe
or-or cruising around on my hog?
- What hog?
- Ah-ha!
Exactly.
Where's my hog?!
Where do you think you're going?
I have had it!
From now on,
no one has to do anything.
We could all just do
whatever we want
and I want to take
a bubble bath!
Fine!
So, that's a "yes"
on the concert?
Come on, come on.
(sighs)
Are you going to be
in there all day?
If I feel like it.
Fine. Just so you know,
when I'm done in the garage
I'm using the bathroom
whether you're in here or not.
Mom, I think we should go
to Aunt Helen's funeral.
I mean,
she was a good woman.
It's the least we can do.
I don't know what you're trying
to pull, but I don't like it.
Am I the only one
that cared about her?
You're the good one.
Enjoy your moment in the sun.
Now, get out of here.
This is me time.
Hey, Reese,
which one stinks more?
What's your problem?
You couldn't keep your
big mouth shut
until after the funeral.
I'll have to wait
for another relative
to die to bury this thing.
It could be weeks.
You'll think of something.
No, I won't.
You have good ideas all the time
but for me, this was special.
Hey! You can't leave
this mess here.
I've got a guest coming over.
Too bad. Thanks to you, no one
has to do anything anymore.
It's anarchy, baby.
That's the word, right?
Um... Mom?
I was just wondering
if you could wash
this shirt for me?
(laughing)
You must be joking.
But you're the only one
that knows how to use
the washer and dryer
without getting shocked.
Please?
Well... since you said please.
There you go.
All washed.
I think you've been
in the garage long enough.
(chuckling)
Okay.
(electrical crackling)
Gosh!
Well, no, no, no.
You are going to get
your own outlet.
Uh... okay, here we go.
Okay... okay, here we are.
(laughing)
Come on.
Gotcha!
Oh.
No, not my problem today.
(claps hands)
(chuckling)
(music playing loudly)
Hand me that loofah.
He wants juice.
Go get your own juice.
You said I'm not supposed to.
(sighing):
You're right.
Okay, from now on
you are officially old enough
to get your own juice.
Poof.
(music continues)
Darn it.
Mom, I spilled!
So? Clean it up.
Green apple soap.
Girls like green apples, right?
Oh, man,
she got my pants wet, too.
(music continues)
(loudly):
Hello?
Is Malcolm here?
(gasps)
Is Malcolm here?!
Huh?
Malcolm?!
Julie:
Malcolm?
Julie!
Nothing.
(screaming)
Oh, my God!
Are you okay?
I just wanted to be nice.
People told me not to come
to your house.
I thought they were
just being silly!
Julie, I'm sorry.
Things aren't usually like this.
Just give me a minute
and I'll be ready to go.
I don't want to go anymore!
Just leave me alone!
(music continues)
(music stops)
How could you let her see me
in my underwear?
Mom, this has gone too far.
You have to do something.
It's not supposed to be like this.
We're not supposed
to injure my friends.
We're not supposed to let people
see me in my underpants.
We're supposed to be there
for each other.
Like when a family member dies,
and we're supposed to go
to their funeral?
I'll be in my room.
Then she slid into the trash
and ran off.
I swear, this whole family
is falling apart.
Yes! I knew
this moment would come.
They don't have
their scapegoat around
so everything goes to hell.
No one realized that I'm the one
who held this family together.
Without me to blame everything on
they don't know what to do
with themselves.
A scapegoat... thanks.
Mom thinks...
He's right.
This family needs a scapegoat.
I started this, so I should be
the one to end it.
I did a terrible thing today.
I tore this family apart
and I'm really sorry for that
but...
it's not half as bad...
as what Reese did!
Oh, my God!
Was this Dewey's present?
Dewey:
Present?
Lois:
Reese, how could you?
Do you know how
expensive this was?
Hal?
I'm on it.
That was a terrible
thing to do
to your little brother.
He was going to bury it
with Aunt Helen.
You were going to make
Aunt Helen spend eternity
with a crushed Mighty Man?
M-Mighty Man?
I can't believe you.
This is a whole new low, Reese.
First of all,
this is all circumstantial.
I don't know how that thing
got in my backpack.
As for this Aunt Helen business,
no one knows what I would've
done at that funeral
because we're not going.
Who says we're not going?
You did.
Well, you can guess again.
You are going to march
right up to that coffin
and apologize
to that poor, dead woman.
We all are.
All right,
everyone in the car as is.
We'll have to drive creatively,
but we might make the end.
Let's go. Chop, chop,
here we go!
Egg! Come on!
Aunt Helen used to say
(raspy-voiced): "Oh, you're going
to miss me when I'm gone."
And, uh, by the looks
of today's turnout
I could see it wasn't
just an idle threat.
(whispering): Yeah, Francis,
your father's giving a speech
and it's actually kind of good.
Can I get my phone back?
I'm almost done, sweetie.
Oh, Aunt Helen looks just lovely.
You turn right back around, mister!
You'll never guess what Reese did.
Well, it's been
a pretty productive day.
I madeJulie Rulerman hate me.
Reese is going to kill me
the second we get home
and right now
Aunt Helen is personally
bad-mouthing me to God.
You want some more water,
Uncle Louie?
Sure.
I need someone to put in
a good word for me.