02 Evangelion 2.22 You Can (Not) Advance -
Anime 2009 720p [H264-mp4] English
Start entry sequence.
Initializing LCL ionization.
Plug depth stable at default value.
Autonomous systems are a go.
Boot-up voltage has cleared the threshold.
Launch prerequisites achieved.
Synchronization rate requirements are a go.
Pilot, please specify linguistic
norm for cognitive functions.
Well, it's my first time,
so I'll go with Japanese.
Roger.
I guess we weren't able to issue
you the new model in time.
I hate how this thing's tight in the chest.
On top of which, we're sending you out to
fight in an Eva that was thrown together.
So I'm really sorry about that.
You finally let me get in
the pilot's seat, so we're good.
You're a problem child, after all.
Well, we're counting on you.
It's moving! It's moving!
This is great! So exciting!
Now, then!
Evangelion Provisional Unit 05, activate!
Defend the Limbo Area at all costs!
We cannot allow it to escape from Acheron!
How could a containment system
as secure as Cocytus be neutralized?
It was within the realm of possibility.
On its own, humanity is incapable
of holding the Angels in check.
The analysis following
the permafrost excavation
of the 3rd Angel was so extensive,
all that was left were some bones.
And this was the conclusion.
That's it. Good luck!
- Happiness won't come walking to you -
- That's why you have to walk to it -
- One step a day, three
steps in three days -
- Three steps forward and two steps back -
- Go at life with a one-two punch -
Ooh, here it comes! Deploy field!
Target inbound. Eva Unit-05
is about to engage the hostile.
Oh, man!
This thing is so not responsive!
I guess that just leaves
brute force as my only option!
Upper outer wall integrity compromised!
The final seal is about to be breached!
Target has broken through Limbo Area.
Now moving into Acheron.
Get Unit-05 to do something!
You're not getting away from me!
Ow! This hurts real bad, but...
It's fun, so it's all good!
No time left.
And this unit can't take much more.
And the artificial arms
were forcibly synchronized,
so they're not as powerful.
Oh, fine!
I'll let you have an arm!
Drop dead already!
Target obliterated.
Unit-05 has been vaporized.
Pilot appears to have been ejected.
So, Unit-05's self-destruct program
functioned without a hitch...
This was always part of the plan,
but I feel bad about involving
kids to carry out adult agendas.
Ow, that hurt...
Synchronizing with an Eva is
more brutal than they'd said.
Well, as long as I'm alive, it's all good.
I feel awkward involving adults
for the sake of my own goals...
Farewell, Eva Unit-05.
You served well.
It's been three years, hasn't it?
Since we last came here together.
I ran away that time and...
I haven't been here since.
It doesn't seem real to me
that Mom was laid to rest here.
I don't even remember her face.
People deal with life by
letting their memories fade.
But there are also some
things that we must never forget.
And Yui taught me those things,
which are to be treasured.
I come here to reaffirm those things.
You don't have any
photos of her or anything?
None remain.
Even this grave is just for show.
There's no body here.
So you threw everything away,
just like my teacher said.
It's all in my heart and mind.
That's enough for now.
It's time. I'll be returning without you.
Dad!
Um...
I'm glad I got to talk to you today.
Are you?
Well, Shinji?
You were worried about this and that,
but it wasn't so bad when
you actually saw him, right?
It's good that you came instead of
being wishy-washy at home, right?
It was a visit to your
mother's grave, after all.
You just dragged me
out here, Miss Misato.
That's because, deep down,
you wanted to come.
Be at least a little honest with yourself.
Being honest with myself will
only make me more miserable.
You lived up to everyone's
expectation and saved us.
Have more confidence in yourself.
I'm sure your father also recognizes
you for what you've accomplished.
Yes? Katsuragi.
Whoa-oa-oa!
What did you say?!
The Seventh Angel has been detected
off the coast of Sagami Bay.
Area 2 Division engaging target.
State of emergency
declared three minutes ago.
I've got a visual on it, too.
Currently transporting Unit-01 pilot.
Implement Task 03 right
away, prioritizing Unit-00.
Negative. Task 02 has
already been implemented.
Task 02?!
Don't tell me...!
Just as I thought! Unit-02!
Wow! One shot to take out the core!
No! That was a decoy!
Situation terminated!
Eva Unit-02 currently in
transit via Main Sagami Line 1.
No change to ETA to Depot 9.
Whoowee! So Unit-02's red, huh?
Its color's not the only
thing that's different.
Ultimately, Unit-00 and Unit-01
are just the prototype and the test-type
used in the developmental process.
But Unit-02 is different.
It's none other than the world's first
real Evangelion, built for actual combat!
The official production model!
Allow me to introduce you
to the Euro Air Force ace,
Captain Asuka Langley Shikinami.
She's the 2nd Girl.
Designated pilot of Eva Unit-02.
Long time no see, Misato.
So that's the Unit-00 pilot, who was
chosen because she's the teacher's pet.
And which one of you is the Unit-01 pilot,
who was chosen because he's daddy's boy?
Uh, um...
What are you, an idiot?!
Not being available in a moment of crisis?!
How blind are you?!
And unguarded, too.
You're not even ashamed that
your Eva wasn't there to fight!
That's what you get from a daddy's boy.
Who the hell does that chick
think she is, anyway?!
A captain already at our age, though?
That's awesome! Beyond awesome!
That's like going from junior high
straight to grad school!
Excuse me.
Is this the right gate for
the Geofront's hub terminal?
Er, yes. You'll have to transfer
at the fourth stop, though.
I've only been gone for two years,
and I feel like Urashima Taro...
Thanks, you're a lifesaver.
By the way, isn't Katsuragi with you?
I'm an old friend of hers.
You're not the only one who knows
what a sloppy sleeper she is, Shinji Ikari.
He's watched her sleep?
Who is that guy?
Man, oh, man, that was one rough job.
The 3rd Angel and Eva Unit-05,
which were outstanding issues,
were disposed of as planned.
The cause, categorically
deemed an accident.
The Marduk Plan at Bethany Base
will come to a standstill now.
All has gone exactly as you had planned.
As for the usual report on
the latest from Seele, just earlier, I...
We took a look at it.
Confirmation of the construction
of Mark 06 proved useful.
Excellent.
Here is the item as promised.
The lost number that had been
stored for safekeeping as the spare.
The waymark that will
entwine God and soul.
Yes.
It will open the door
to Human Instrumentality.
The Key of Nebuchadnezzar.
Then if you'll excuse me,
I'm going to go do my
own thing for a while.
Ryoji Kaji. Chief Inspection Officer.
Is he a man that can be trusted?
Have you lost a little weight, Ritsy?
Wrong. I've gained 1,570 grams.
I'd love to see for myself.
I wouldn't mind, but this
room is being monitored.
No problem. I already have fake
footage running on the system.
Thoroughly prepared as ever, aren't you?
I just don't like to lose.
But you've lost.
There's a scary lady watching us.
Long time no see, Ryo.
Hey, it's been a while.
What the hell are you doing here?
You're assigned to Euro, aren't you?
I'm here on a special assignment.
I'll be at Headquarters for a while.
The three of us can hang out together
again. Just like when we were students.
I have no interest in
going back to those days!
I only came to see Ritsuko!
About Asuka. I got HR's okay. Bye!
That was blatant jealousy.
You've got a shot at her here, Ryo.
Well, we'll have to see about that.
Asuka Shikinami...
I had no idea some people were
actually happy to pilot an Eva.
I'm back.
Wait, what the hell is this?!
My room...
How rude!
That's my stuff.
But then, what about my stuff?
Wait, what are you doing here, Shikinami?
What are you, an idiot?
It means they're giving you the boot.
Well, when you consider who's
the more accomplished one here,
the decision was obvious.
You can't be serious!
But why are Japanese
rooms so cramped?!
I couldn't even fit
half of my stuff in here!
And why do Japanese people
totally lack any sense of security?
I don't know how you people
live in rooms without locks!
Unbelievable!
That's because the Japanese spirit is
about being perceptive and considerate.
Miss Misato!
You are so annoying!
Hurry up and get lost
along with the trash.
Oh, but Shin's staying here, too.
What?!
What you and Shin lack is
appropriate communication skills.
As fellow pilots, you need to live
under the same roof and make nice.
That's an order.
Okay, all together now!
Thank you for the meal!
A cold beer after a hot bath
is still the best thing ever!
Th-Th-There's some
weird animal in the bath!
It's a kind of bird called penguins.
His name is Pen Pen.
You pervert!
Jerk! You're sick! Unbelievable!
They're starting to open up more.
This is why I hate boys!
Blah
Don't you, Pen Pen?
"I'm not like them, either!"
"I'm special!"
"That's why, just like before..."
You have to keep going it alone, Asuka.
I guess Dad still won't answer the phone.
A social studies field trip?
Kaji's taking you?
Yes. He said I should
invite everyone else along, too.
Nothing good will come of
having anything to do with that guy.
Then I'm gonna pass!
No, you're not. "Harmony
is the greatest of virtues."
You go, too, Asuka.
Is that an order, too?
Here we are, with the Tabgha
Moonbase right in front of our noses,
and yet, they refuse
us permission to land.
The Seele certainly can be nasty.
The construction methods being used
on the Mark 06 differ from the others.
Getting to ascertain that is enough.
But there weren't supposed to be any
plans for construction beyond Unit-05.
There are likely still undisclosed
Apocrypha of the Dead Sea Scrolls.
Seele intends to follow their
script based on those writings.
But even Seele must be aware
of Nerv's ultimate goal at this point.
Even if they are, we have
but to follow our own path.
Though it may mean turning
against the Word of God.
Is that a person?
Surely not...
Nice to meet you, Father.
Awesome! This is beyond awesome!
Perpetual conservation of
the marine life that was lost
and restoration of the
oceans that had turned red!
Truly, a forbidden sanctuary carrying
out grand godlike experimental projects!
Just getting to scratch the surface
and tour even a small part of it is...
Truly, it's like, this is
what good friends are for!
Awesome!
Blah
If you're going to thank
someone, thank Mr. Kaji.
Here's where things get complicated.
Huh?
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
C-Cold! Cold!
Not again.
Nooo!
I can't take any more of this...
What a huge tank!
Amazing!
So these are the creatures
from before the Second Impact.
Holy...! They're alive!
Awesome! Beyond awesome!
Ooh, here's one with
somethin' on its back!
I hear they're called "turtles."
"Turtuls"?
Look at the kiddies getting all excited.
Talk about idiotic.
I'm glad you were able
to come with us, Ayanami.
Are you okay now, health wise?
Yes.
I finished my allotment,
so I'm fine today.
It's so cramped in there.
They should go swim in the bigger areas.
They can't.
They can only survive in there.
Just like me.
Time to eat!
This is good. I didn't expect that.
Yeah, excellent job on
the grilling and seasoning.
To think the 90% artificial meat can
become this tasty when cooked right.
It's truly astounding!
Shinji, that's a hidden
talent ya got there.
Miss Misato only goes
for microwavable foods,
so it's either I cook or nothing.
Women love men who know
their way around a kitchen, Shinji.
You hear that?
Nuh-uh! I'm not gonna cook!
That's no job for a man!
Talk about old-fashioned. So idiotic.
The hell d'you say?!
It's important to have yer principles!
That's even more idiotic.
The hell d'you say?!
Sorry, Ayanami, was it not to your taste?
No, I just don't eat meat.
Why do you Japanese apologize when
you haven't even done anything wrong?!
And you!
Living things eat other
living things to survive!
That's precious life there,
so clean your plate!
Are you trying to pick a fight,
Teacher's Pet?!
Comin' through, comin' through.
In that case, I'll just help myself.
Ya aren't gettin' any!
Greedy bastard! Get away from me!
Moron!
Idiotic.
Then, how about some miso soup?
It'll warm you up.
It's delicious.
To think that this is our Mother Earth.
I can't look at it. It breaks my heart.
However, there are also those who
wished for this miserable state.
Because it's a world barred to man,
cleansed and untainted by original sin.
I would rather have a
chaotic world tainted by man.
Chaos is merely a human impression.
The world is composed
entirely of harmony and order.
So, it is the human heart that
throws the world into confusion.
It's hard for me to imagine
that this ocean used
to be blue before I was born.
It's amazing that we were even
able to restore the environment
to the point where we
humans could live in it.
But this sea breeze...
It smells kind of weird
and fishy, doesn't it?
It's the smell of decaying marine life.
It's proof that they were alive.
Not like that red water with nothing in it.
This is how the real
ocean's supposed to be.
By rights, this world should be
vast and filled with all kinds of life.
And I wanted you guys to know that.
It makes me happy somehow.
Miss Misato should have come, too.
Katsuragi would never come.
Because it would remind her.
Of what?
The Second Impact...
Have you ever asked
Katsuragi why she joined Nerv?
Katsuragi's father was
apparently the sort of man
who lived for his research,
lived in his dreams.
And she used to hate her father for that.
I think she may have even despised him.
So you don't get along with your father.
You're the same as me.
She's the same as me.
But in the end,
she was saved by her father.
Being a survivor can mean a lot of things.
You have to accept the
sacrifice of those who died
and bear the burden of what they stood for.
That's all the more true
if you're the sole survivor.
You're not the only one who's got it rough.
Target detected by Mauna Kea
Observatories three minutes ago.
Currently entering orbital elements.
Surveillance Satellite 3
has a visual on the target.
Putting it on screen at
maximum magnification.
An AT field powerful enough
to bend light? That's phenomenal.
So, where do we expect it to land?
Here, of course. Right?
The Magi are also recalculating.
Probability of a direct hit
on Nerv HQ is 99.9999%.
The aerial N2 bombs are
having no effect whatsoever.
So, no adjusting its trajectory.
Its AT field is pushed out
to one concentrated point,
and the energy from its
descent will add to that as well.
So the Angel itself is acting as a bomb.
In the event the
8th Angel scores a direct hit,
the estimated diameter
of the blast is 420,000.
With a geoid deviation of -15,000.
New Tokyo-3 will be vaporized.
The Central Dogma will be completely
exposed, to say nothing of the Geofront.
Where's Commander Ikari?
Signals in the upper atmosphere
are unstable due to the Angel.
We can't reach him at this time.
We'll have no choice but
to make the call ourselves here.
Notify the Japanese government
as well as all ministries.
Under Nerv's authority,
we are issuing Special Declaration D-17.
Immediately commence the evacuation
of all residents within a 120km radius.
Not a problem.
People connected to the government have
already begun scrambling to evacuate.
Evacuation of civilians
within city limits completed.
Evacuation of noncombatants and
Class D Workers has been completed
in accordance with Departmental Warning C.
We've asked Matsushiro
to handle the backup of the Magi.
So, what's the plan?
Even our Evas aren't capable of flying...
Severe spatial distortion also makes
sniping from various angles impossible.
There's nothing we can do
against a monster like this.
Are you serious?
Yes, I am.
Can this plan really be called a strategy?
Even the Magi have verified that the
probability of failure is a little over 99%.
Even if it succeeds, we'll lose three Evas.
Speaking for the Technology Division,
that is absolutely unacceptable.
Our chance of success isn't zero.
Better to be down-to-earth and
work hard than wait for a miracle.
We should make protecting
Lilith and Unit-01 our top priority.
I have no intention of waiting.
We're going to create
a miracle of man's own volition!
Colonel Katsuragi!
I am currently the ranking officer here.
It's my decision to make.
Besides, my job is to wipe out the angels.
Your job? Your personal grudge, you mean?
That's what your vendetta
against the Angels is.
What?! Catch it with our hands?!
That's right. As the Angel comes flying,
you'll deploy your Eva's AT field
at maximum and catch it directly.
The target is disguising its location,
so you won't be able to expect
an accurate calculation of the trajectory
based on compensated observation.
In order to give ourselves multiple
options as the situation dictates,
this mission will involve all three
Evas being deployed simultaneously.
You're wasting your time!
I can destroy it on my own!
That'll be impossible.
A single Eva won't be able to cover
the vast area within which
the Angel is estimated to land.
What is this positioning based on?
Woman's intuition.
How arbitrary is that!
Um, what's our chance of success?
I'd have to say, God only knows.
That's exactly why these millstones
around my neck will get in the way!
I'm more than up to the task
of protecting mankind on my own!
Your performance in single-combat
isn't what this mission needs.
So you refuse to acknowledge my talent?
That's not it.
I need all three of you on this...
to create a miracle.
All Evas currently operating
on live power sources.
Unit 5 is in position. Situation, green.
Power transmission is nominal.
Currently standing by
at designated location.
Construction of Temporary Power
Storage Facility 305 is complete.
Connection made with the
New Gotenba Substation.
Station coming online.
- Continuing to lay down auxiliary cables.
- Unit-00 internal power charged to over 105%.
- Auxiliary power extension cables have arrived.
- Commencing system check.
Team 8, please get them connected quickly.
Roger. Circuits green.
Transmission voltage nominal.
Checking Unit-01 connector link.
No abnormalities detected.
Respiration and heart rates are normal.
Final medical check has been cleared.
Being inside the Eva...
I wonder why.
It's strangely calming in here,
even at a time like this.
Have I gotten used to
being in here already?
I wonder why.
It feels warm and familiar...
Is it the smell?
How my mom smelled?
How Ayanami smells?
Calculating target's trajectory.
And here it comes.
All Evas in your start positions.
Since the secondary data is unreliable,
priority from here on out will be
given to your on site discretion.
Everything we've got is
riding on you and the Evas.
Target approaching.
Distance, approximately 20,000.
All right then, start the operation.
Go.
Target's AT field is transforming!
Trajectory changing!
Estimated point of impact adjusted by 205.
Target accelerating!
What the hell?
It's faster than they'd estimated!
No good! I won't make it in time!
I'll manage things from my end.
Miss Misato!
Emergency course configuration! 605 to 675!
Yes, ma'am!
Next! 1072 to 1078! Stand by!
Target morphing! Distance, 12,000!
AT field at maximum!
Daddy's Boy!
Unit-02, get the core.
I know that!
Don't order me around!
I missed?!
Damn sore loser, scurrying around!
30 seconds left!
Hurry, Asuka!
I know!
Teacher's Pet?!
Hurry...
Asuka!
I know what to do, damn you!
And here's one more!
Thank you, you guys.
Radio systems are back online.
Incoming call from Commander Ikari.
Patch him through.
You have my apologies.
Decisions I made at my discretion
have resulted in damage to three Evas,
as well as injury to their pilots.
I take full responsibility for it.
That's fine. In light of
the target's destruction,
this level of damage might
actually be considered fortunate.
Yes, you did well for
us, Colonel Katsuragi.
Thank you very much.
Patch me through to Unit-01's pilot.
I heard what happened.
You did well, Shinji.
What? Yes, sir...
Then, Colonel Katsuragi,
I will leave the rest to you.
Yes, sir.
Expedite the recovery of the three Evas.
Priority goes to Unit-01.
Transport to Emergency Cage 99.
I couldn't do anything...
on my own.
Being alone has always
been the norm for me, and yet...
Solitude shouldn't bother me, and yet...
H-Hey...
Don't turn this way.
Daddy's Boy, let me stay here,
just for a little while.
Um... Miss... Shikinami?
You got caught up in the moment
and called me by name today.
I'll make a special exception.
You can call me Asuka.
I'll call you Stupid Shinji, too.
Then... um...
Asuka, why do you pilot the Eva...?
What a silly question.
Shut up, Stupid Shinji.
I pilot the Eva for myself.
What about you?
I don't really know.
What are you, an idiot?
That's just how you avoid
owning up to whatever it is, right?
Maybe I want Dad to praise me.
He praised me for the first time today.
For the first time, I
felt happy to be praised.
I wonder if Dad recognizes me
for my accomplishments now.
Maybe it's just like Miss Misato said.
You...
really are an idiot.
Did you watch it?
All righty, time to eat!
It's the best part of school, after all!
What?! You didn't bring us lunch?!
I was doing homework this morning
and I didn't have time to make it!
And because of that, you
expect me to go without lunch?!
Like I said, I'll be sure
to make lunch tomorrow!
What's this? Another marital spat?
No, it's not!
Asuka, let me borrow
your face washing soap.
Enough already, Misato! Get your own!
Cheapskate!
All righty, time to eat!
Woohoo! Let's dig in!
Hmm. It's so-so today.
But it'd be even better
if he hadn't slacked off that day.
Um, Asuka?
Would you mind if I joined you?
No, but I'm not sharing my lunch.
Here, this is for you.
You never seem to have lunch, so...
Thank you.
I'm so glad I worked up
the nerve to talk to you.
Hikari, was it?
You can have the rest.
Whew, I'm stuffed!
Thank you for the meal!
That's a late lunch.
Th-Thanks.
So I hear Shinji makes your lunches?
Well, you're not the
home cooking type anyway.
I suppose not. Unlike you,
with time on your hands,
I have boatloads of work to do
as a manager in the trenches.
You're as serious as ever.
I mean, that's your strength,
but it's also your weakness.
Like the other day.
I heard that you went at it with Ritsy.
Relax a little more.
Unfortunately, my plate's
always full with duty and obligations.
If you're too tense,
you'll never find a guy.
Nobody asked you!
"Thank you."
Words of gratitude.
Words I'd never spoken before.
I'd never even said it to him...
Rise!
Bow!
Be seated!
Ayanami's absent again, huh? No matter.
She seemed well yesterday.
Now, I'm going to give you back
the test from the other day,
I wonder what happened.
Just like me.
They can only survive in there...
What did she mean?
Rei.
Time for a meal.
Yes, sir.
Commander Ikari.
What is it?
Are meals enjoyable?
Yes.
Is there pleasure in
eating with someone else?
Yes.
Cooking dishes is delightful...
Is that right?
Yes.
Commander Ikari,
how about having a meal with
Ikari and the others sometime?
No, I have no time for such...
Honey, take care of Shinji for me...
All right, I'll go.
Simulated synch is normal for all pilots.
Picking up no psychological contamination.
LCL osmotic pressure
clears Categorization B.
Jeez, this is so boring!
If no Angels come, we're stuck
doing checks all day! Totally not cool.
I don't see the problem.
We're doing all this work so we can build a
peaceful daily life free of Angels, you know.
Whee!
Glorying in our repetitive daily lives:
in a today just like yesterday,
a tomorrow probably just like today.
That's something to be
grateful for, actually.
Checks complete. All monitors
coming in loud and clear.
Good work, you three. You
can come on out now.
Back up to file 101.
Commencing LCL drain in three minutes.
This may not be for me to say,
but such severe damage is going
to hinder our ability to run operations.
Couldn't we just scrap the Vatican Treaty?
I know.
With each country only allowed
possession of a maximum of three Evas,
there's no leeway in operational units.
Even now, our repair work
is being prioritized for Unit-01.
We're just barely managing
by juggling all the spare parts,
so we don't even know when
we'll be able to repair Unit-00.
The nationalistic ego of every
country is tangled up in that Treaty.
Getting it revised will
be nearly impossible.
On top of which, with
their loss of Unit-05,
Euro and Russia seem to be embroiling
Asia in their various allegations.
It gets to be something of a pain
when politics enters the picture.
There's too much to do before we can
even get around to protecting mankind.
Move! Move!
Ooh, ow... That hurt...
My glasses, my glasses...
Um...
Oh, sorry. Are you okay?
Hello. Mari here.
Yes, I seem to have glided off target.
It looks like I'm in a school of some sort.
What?!
Well, you told me
to enter into Japan covertly!
Won't you have the
Euro people work this out?
Just be there for my
extraction later, okay?
Thanks.
You smell good. I can smell LCL on you.
You're interesting.
Well, mum's the word.
Okay, little Nerv doggy?
Huh? That's strange...
Hey. How about going on a date for once?
I'm a guy.
No problem.
Gender has nothing to do with love.
I'm kidding.
Here.
The smell of dirt...
Worn out already?
I expect to get the labor I paid for.
Paid for? You mean that can of coffee?
And you called this a date.
I thought you were a
more serious person than this.
For an adult, being more
devious than not is just about perfect.
If I remember right, these
are watermelons, aren't they?
Yeah. Cute, right?
It's my hobby.
Making things or growing things is great.
It makes you see and
understand all kinds of things.
Like about enjoyment.
And about suffering, too, right?
Do you hate suffering?
I don't like it.
Did you find something that you enjoyed?
That's fine, too.
But people who know about suffering
are capable of being kind
to others that much more.
And that's not the same as being weak.
Do you like Katsuragi?
M-Miss Misato?
Uh, well... I don't not like her.
Protect Katsuragi for me.
That's something I can't do. Only you can.
Please.
Morning.
Ayanami!
A greeting?
From Ayanami?
Ayanami, are you okay now?
Yes, I'm fine today.
What happened to your hand?
Dr. Akagi put them on for me just earlier.
What were you doing?
It's a secret.
I'll tell you once I get
a little better at it.
Rei's changed.
The idea of her doing something
for someone else is mind-boggling.
What could have brought this on?
Maybe... it's love!
Surely not. Impossible.
I wonder if Idiot Shinji
would prefer it to be milder.
I'm back!
Oh? Misato, you're early.
I have to go right back to HQ.
I only came home for
a bath and change of clothes.
Ooh!
Whoa!
Oh, my, my! Are you going
to cook for Shin, too?
What?!
No! Um, it's for a girl...
Y-Yeah, it's for Hikari!
First Rei and now you.
Getting romantic all of a sudden.
What? Don't lump me
in with that teacher's pet!
Hmm, I suppose I shouldn't.
Rei seems to have something
more ambitious planned, after all.
What do you mean?
It looks like she wants to be the cupid
who brings Commander
Ikari and Shin together.
"Invite everyone to a dinner party
and serve a home-cooked meal"
seems to be her plan of attack.
It's so direct, it's going to pack a punch.
Seriously, bringing that family
closer together is no easy task.
That girl's doing this for Idiot Shinji?
It's a surprise, so no telling Shin, okay?
As if I would!
Vaporized?!
Eva Unit-04 and Branch 2 were vaporized?
This is data from ground zero at T plus 10.
It's terrible.
The satellite lets us verify
that the AT field collapsed,
but the specifics remain unknown.
So Unit-04 was at the center,
as we'd suspected.
Tell me that our Evas are fine.
Unit-04 was...!
Unit-04 was the testbed
for a new internal engine
that was meant to solve our
operational time limit issues.
Or so I've heard.
Nerv North America's R&D Intel
hasn't been extensively
disclosed even to Dr. Akagi.
Those who would know are...
Eva Unit-04.
It was an experimental
unit aimed at acquiring data
for the development of a next-generation
Eva. Anything could have happened to it.
But...
Was it really an accident?
Gimme three of these, ma'am.
It's unusual for you to treat us, Toji.
Yer so serious... I never thought you'd come
hang out with us for a cheap snack, either.
Why don't you be honest and say
that your little sister's gotten better?
Shaddup!
Keep yer mouth shut 'bout
what's none of yer business! Moron!
Say, Ikari.
So, Unit-03's coming to Japan?
It is? I haven't heard anything.
Rumor is, the US suddenly
insisted that we take it,
along with making us do
the activation test.
Well, I guess you rank and file
pilots don't need to know about it.
Say, who do you think will be piloting it?
I don't know. I haven't heard anything.
It must be so great to be a pilot!
I wish they'd pick me!
Don't look at me.
Try asking Miss Misato.
Damn, I didn't win.
Evangelion Unit-05 was lost earlier...
And now, Unit-04 has similarly been lost.
The loss of the two units will
hinder the progress of our plans, but...
It is within correctable limits.
There should be no problem.
The American government has
insisted on offering Eva-03 to you.
Your country's government
is amenable to this as well.
It's a state-of-the-art unit.
It should be good enough
to be your main fire power.
The elimination of Angels is
being executed on an ongoing basis.
An untested unit cannot be trusted.
If you would approve the additional
supplementary budget to repair Unit-00...
The prototype's function
is beginning to grow obsolete.
Surely, you have no need of it.
Indeed. There are other
matters that should be given priority.
The true Evangelion that we desire...
With its birth and the resurrection of Lilith
the time of the covenant will be upon us.
The necessary rites must
be performed by then.
For the sake of the
Human Instrumentality Project.
I am aware of this.
All will go according to Seele's plan.
The true Evangelion.
To serve as its forerunners
until its completion...
That's basically the job of all
the current units, including Unit-01.
And that's the Mark 06?
So they've finally decided they want
to create a real god instead of false ones.
Yes.
We must hasten the awakening of Unit-01.
Eva Unit-02's core unit
separation complete.
Why is my Unit-02 being
put into containment?!
You know what the Vatican Treaty is, right?
This is the condition in
exchange for getting Unit-03.
Unit-00's still in for repairs,
so put it into containment!
Euro still has possession
of the pass to Unit-02.
There's nothing we can do about it.
And it has no designated pilot now, either.
Sit tight until we receive
further word from Euro.
But no one can pilot it except me.
The Evas are combat weapons.
There's a backup for everything.
That includes the pilot.
No, it can't be...
But this is the one place
I belong in the entire world...
The Evas mirror what's in our hearts.
What was that?
You don't have to be dependent on the Eva.
There's happiness for you outside the Eva.
Don't patronize me!
You're just the teacher's pet!
I was chosen to be a pilot on
my merits, because I'm a genius!
I'm not like you two, who got
in through your connections!
I'm just tied to it.
I just don't have any ties with
people except through the Eva.
Shut up!
Commander Ikari just favors you,
because you're a prim doll,
who does everything he says, right?!
I'm not a doll.
You are a doll!
Have a little more self-awareness!
You've got some nerve for a doll.
I've got just one question for you.
What do you think of that idiot?
Idiot?
"Idiot" as in "Idiot Shinji," of course.
Ikari?
Well?
I don't really know.
This is the problem with you Japanese!
Say what you mean!
I don't know.
But being with Ikari makes
me feel all warm inside.
I want Ikari to feel all warm inside, too.
I want him to get along
with Commander Ikari
and feel all warm inside.
I get it.
Seriously! Talk about
profoundly ultra-idiotic!
That means she likes him!
I can't wait for this dinner party.
But I wonder if Ayanami's
cooking is going to be okay...
I wish Father would come, too.
The first unmanned solo
activation test of the Dummy System...
So that's the Dummy System.
It is ostensibly nothing more
than a support system for the pilot,
but it is not only capable of
autonomous control on its own,
but it can even generate an
AT field out of an unmanned unit.
It is apparently more humane
than making children pilot them.
There's something about it
that just rubs me the wrong way!
It's a black box part direct
from Golgotha Base, after all.
So it's remained a mystery to us.
Entrusting our Evas to something
so sketchy just boggles my mind!
Are you saying the Evas are safe in the
hands of the pilots because they're human?
Shinji sure has your trust.
Or rather, I guess it's because
of Shinji that you can say that.
Never mind that.
What about Intel on the organization
above us called Seele or something?
Anything you can tell me?
If you want to snoop around
about that project, I'd advise against it.
That's not an option for me.
The Human Instrumentality Project...
What is Nerv trying to
do behind the scenes?
That's...
something I'd like to know, too.
We haven't had a meal together in ages,
and all we talk about is work, work, work!
Things are different
from when we were students.
There's so much more that we're
aware of... burdens we've taken on.
I guess neither of us can afford
to think only of ourselves anymore.
And Shinji and the others are loaded
down with an even greater burden.
Yeah.
It's too much for kids to have to bear.
But we have no choice
but to depend on them.
Yes?
Yes, I know.
I'll make my decision by midnight.
Ritsy?
Yup. She's hounding me
about the Unit-03 test pilot.
Personnel decisions are
your responsibility, after all.
I know that, but...
The schedule set for the
arrival of Unit-03...
Of all days, it's coming on this day.
The day they scheduled
the Unit-03 activation test for is...
the day the teacher's
pet had picked out.
Up we go!
I see. So you've settled on Asuka.
Yes, I'll head for
Matsushiro on the last flight out.
I'll leave the rest to you, Maya.
Yes, ma'am!
Um, Dr. Akagi?
I'd like to get a message
to the Second Girl.
Please.
You have one new message.
First message.
Here, Rei, you can talk now.
Damn it!
Thank you.
What is she, an idiot?!
I'm only doing this because
I want to pilot the Eva.
If I like Unit-03, have
it repainted red, okay?
Good morning, Aida.
Hey yo.
Oh? Where's Toji?
He's at the hospital in Odawara today.
He said his little
sister's being discharged.
Oh, right.
Message for you from Toji.
"Don't ya worry 'bout it anymore.
My sis's grateful, too."
That's what he said.
It's great how things
have worked out, huh, Ikari?
Yeah.
You've been invited over
by Ayanami today, right?
Talk about lucky, you bastard!
Whoa! I can't breathe!
Mission director of the manned activation
testing of the Eva Unit-03 has arrived
and is currently heading
toward the main control room.
Temporary above-ground cage and restraint
system checked. No abnormalities detected.
Connector contact verified.
Main power supply current switch complete.
Entry plug anchored in insertion position.
Checks done up through 1350
on the list. No problems found.
Roger. Resume the countdown.
Resuming countdown.
All ground crew personnel begin evacuation.
Test pilot medical checkups completed.
Currently standing by in
mobile quarantine chamber.
Looks like I can hand over the
rest to Ritsuko without any problems.
Maintenance Team 6, evacuation complete.
Secure line? From Asuka?
What's up, Asuka?
Thoughts before the show starts?
I just felt like having a private
chat with you for some reason.
I see.
I want to let you know again that
I appreciate what you're doing today.
Thank you.
You don't need to thank me.
It's the duty of the elite to help
the ignorant masses, that's all.
And I'm not big on eating
with everyone anyway.
And it's exhausting to have
to pretend you're enjoying yourself
along with everyone else.
And I didn't want to have to sit
around watching others be happy.
And all I care about is piloting the Eva.
And I like being by myself to begin with.
And I had no use for phony friends.
And there's never been anyone
who's seen me for the real me.
And as long as I have
the top performance scores,
I can make a living at Nerv.
But some things happened recently
that made me think being
around other people isn't all bad.
It's so not me, though.
That's not true.
Because you have a kind heart.
You're the first one I've
ever talked to like this.
I feel better somehow.
It feels nice to talk to someone.
I had no idea.
This world is brimming full of
fun things you have no idea about.
You should enjoy it.
Yeah, you're right.
Thank you, Misato.
By the way, it's great
that it's red, but...
Don't you think this plug
suit for the test...
is too revealing?
Begin entry sequence.
LCL ionization, pressure
levels... status green.
Stage One Excited State holding steady.
Plug sensor, nominal.
Inspected values are
within the error range.
Roger. Shift to Phase 2 operations.
Initiate secondary connection.
I hadn't realized... I know how to laugh.
Plug depth is now over 100!
Psychological contamination
levels are now in the red zone!
Pilot is descending below safe depths!
Why did it suddenly do this?!
Pull it back now! At this rate,
the pilot will cease to be a human!
Abort the test!
Shut down all circuits!
Negative! High energy
readings within the Eva!
It can't be...!
An Angel?!
An accidental explosion in Matsushiro?
Damage report!
Unknown. The temporary cage
appears to be the blast epicenter.
Destruction of above-ground
control facilities confirmed.
Immediately dispatch Rescue and 3rd Units.
Get it resolved before the SSDF steps in.
Roger.
Unidentified moving object sighted
southwest of the accident site.
Pattern is orange.
Unable to confirm whether it is an Angel.
Battle Stations, Condition One.
Ikari.
All personnel to
Battle Stations, Condition One.
Place Unit-00 in for repairs on standby.
Launch Unit-01 as soon as it's
been switched out to a dummy plug.
Deployment of 5th Tank Company
to Defensive Line 18 complete.
Connection of main power extension
cable to be complete in two minutes.
Backup mobile strike unit is in position.
Um, what about Miss Misato
and Asuka and the others?
Currently, all efforts are
being made to rescue them.
Don't worry.
But...
Miss Misato isn't here and with no other
Eva... There's nothing I can do by myself.
Operationally, we're fine.
Commander Ikari is directing
this operation himself right now.
Dad is?
We have footage captured near Tomi.
Patching it through to main monitor.
Just as we had feared...
Send shutdown signal.
Force eject the entry plug.
No good. It isn't recognizing the
shutdown or the plug ejection code.
Encroachment of a core-like substance
confirmed near the entry plug area.
We have the pattern analysis.
It's blue.
As of this moment, we are
scrapping Evangelion Unit-03.
Object under surveillance will
be identified as the 9th Angel.
Target approaching.
Prepare to intercept ground-to-ground.
Blockade units, open fire!
It can't be!
An Angel?! This is an Angel?!
That's right, that's your target.
Target?
But this is...
an Eva!
This can't be...
The target is approaching.
You must defeat it.
You call it a target, but...
Isn't Asuka on board?
Asuka is...
Damn it!
The entry plug!
So she is on board!
Armor being corroded
near cervical vertebrae!
Contamination confirmed through Layer 6200!
As we had feared, an invasive type.
This will be tricky.
Unit-01's AT field is unstable!
Life support system malfunctioning!
Any more of this and
the pilot will be in danger!
This is bad! Cut the
neural connections to 28%!
Wait.
But Ikari, the pilot will die at this rate!
Shinji, why won't you fight?
Because... Asuka's on board, Dad!
It doesn't matter.
That's an Angel. It's our enemy.
But I can't do it!
I can't murder her!
You're going to die.
I don't care! Better than killing Asuka!
No matter.
Cut the pilot's synchronization
with Unit-01 across the board.
Ikari?
That's right. Switch control
over to the Dummy System.
But the Dummy System
still has a lot of problems
and without Dr. Akagi's instruction...
It will be of more use
than the current pilot.
Do it!
Yes, sir.
What is this?
What are you doing, Dad?!
Main control system switchover complete.
- Energy conduction efficiency is unimpeded.
- All neural circuits directly connected to Dummy System.
- AT field stable, recovered to Level B.
- Dummy System operational time limit is a maximum of 208 seconds.
Fine. Release the System. Commence attack.
Is this the power of the Dummy System?
Dummy System functioning normally.
Control limiters being released.
What is this, Dad?
What is this?
What are you doing?!
Damn it!
Stop!
Stop, stop, stop, stop,
stop, stop, stop, stop...
stop stop, stop, stop!
What's that sound?
Don't do it!
No!
Found another one over here! A survivor!
- Team 3, delete the data from 807. Quickly!
- Send a rescue team over here, stat!
That's right.
Incinerate all surveillance
recorders in the contaminated zone.
- Close Route 18 to all traffic!
- Don't let the SSDF in for at least another ten minutes!
I'm alive?
Kaji?
You were lucky, Katsuragi.
What about Ritsuko?
No worries. Her wounds
were more minor than yours.
I see.
Asuka! What about Eva Unit-03?
It was apparently disposed of...
as an Angel.
By Unit-01.
Unit-01's synchronization
circuits have been cut.
What about the ejection signal?
It has been locked out
from inside the plug.
He's literally locked himself in there.
Don't do this, Shinji!
Think about what you're doing!
Don't make me even angrier
by saying things like that.
Unit-01 has 285 seconds left.
With that much time, I can
destroy at least half of headquarters.
In his current state,
he might very well do it.
Shinji, please listen to us!
You may have been killed if
Commander Ikari hadn't made his decision!
That doesn't matter.
But it's the truth!
I told you, that doesn't matter!
Dad tried...
That bastard tried to kill Asuka!
Using me!
Why?!
Why?! Why did you do it?!
You don't understand at all, Dad!
I was a fool for trusting you!
You should lose someone
you care about, too, Dad!
Then, you'd understand!
Raise the LCL compression
density right up to the limit.
What?!
We have no time to put
up with a child's tantrum.
I still have the direct control circuits...
Damn it all!
Damn it all...
Ikari, you're always
listening to that, aren't you?
Yeah. It's something Dad used to use.
Just like your glasses, Ayanami.
But he didn't need it anymore,
so he left it behind.
Just like me.
It was at my teacher's place, so I took it.
When I close up my ears,
I can close up my heart.
That way, I don't have to deal
with the nasty world out there.
Nasty world?
That's right.
The world where the father I hate lives.
The world where the scary
Angels and Evas exist.
The world where
I'm forced to do painful things.
The world where Dad doesn't need
me as long as he has the Dummy.
The world where my friends get hurt.
Even so, good things happened, too.
But in the end, it all gets destroyed.
It's a nasty world.
I'm going to turn my back on it now.
I thought that if I did this,
Dad would protect me from the nasty world.
I'd tricked myself into believing that.
Did you try to understand
your father, Ikari?
I did.
Are you sure you didn't just do nothing?
I did try to understand him!
My dad's the one in the wrong!
He's the one who abandoned me!
And so, you're running away
from the things you don't like again.
So what?!
What's wrong with running
away from the things I don't like?!
This place again.
I'm sick of this.
Verify all instructions on
recovering fragments of Unit-03
with the Technology Division.
Her cellular tissue is clear
of any trace of the invasion,
but there's the possibility she was
psychologically contaminated by the Angel.
We have no choice but
to keep her under quarantine.
They wouldn't possibly
do away with her, right?
She's a valuable sample specimen.
They would never.
Come out, Shinji Ikari.
Commander Ikari will see you now.
Insubordination. Seizing an
Eva for your own personal use.
Making crude threats.
These are all criminal acts.
Do you have anything to say for yourself?
Yes.
I do not want to pilot the Eva anymore.
I see. Then leave.
Running away again?
Your dreams are something you
have to sacrifice everything for
and attain for yourself.
No one will do it for you.
Grow up, Shinji.
I don't know what it's supposed
to mean to be a grownup.
It's me. Strike the Third
Boy from the records.
From now on, the primary operator
of Unit-01 will be the Dummy System.
No backup will be necessary.
I guess Rei didn't stop
Shinji from leaving.
I was hoping she'd do something,
since she'd shown signs of changing lately.
The relationships between
those kids is unfathomable.
But now, we're back down
to one pilot again.
Back to square one.
I'm sure you know this,
but even though you've been
stricken from Nerv's records,
you'll still be under surveillance
and your actions will be
restricted pretty heavily.
You forgot this.
Suzuhara and Aida
left you a lot of messages.
They're worried about you.
I don't really want it.
It's something I left behind.
You haven't asked after
Rei or Asuka, either.
The truth is, maybe I don't care
about humanity or the world, either.
Ultimately, I've ended
up in my current position,
but at first, I just wanted to get
a little closer to my late father.
And that's why I signed up with Nerv.
Just like how you piloted the Eva
because you wanted
Commander Ikari to need you.
Which is why I found myself
living vicariously through you.
And I know that you felt burdened by it.
I also know that you've become disillusioned
with your purpose in piloting the Eva.
But even so, I want you to...
That day...
Rei had invited Commander Ikari, too.
She wanted you to become
closer with your father.
She wanted you two to laugh together.
I'll never be able to
laugh with anyone again.
The next stop is Kamigora. Kamigora.
The exits will be to your left.
The Japanese government has
declared a state of emergency.
In accordance with the
emergency regulations,
this train will stop at the
nearest evacuation station.
After disembarking, please head
straight for your designated platform
and board the evacuation incline.
It's an Angel.
Eva Unit-02 containment
measures have been unlocked.
Final safety systems have been disabled.
Core unit automatic
reconfiguration sequence has begun.
Man, it's cold!
There we go.
That's the new model for you!
It even fits me perfectly
in the chest. Feels so good!
The time has come.
All personnel, Battle
Stations, Condition One.
Prepare to intercept ground-to-air.
Target's status?
It has breached the
Old Odawara defensive line.
This is no laughing matter if the shockwave
can be felt all the way down here.
Direct hit on District 4. Damages unknown.
Surface and all armor
systems have been liquefied!
All 24 layers of specialized
armor with one strike?!
The 10th Angel.
The most powerful rejection type...
Its destructive power is
greater than we'd imagined.
This is all-out war!
Put all the fortified city's intercept
equipment to specialized use!
Hold it at bay, even
if it's just for a little while!
Eva Unit-02?! Who's piloting it?!
Unknown! We did not order its launch!
Target still active.
Second wave of attack had no effect.
I don't care! Evacuating
the residents gets top priority!
Authorizing third wave of guided N2
missiles! Send them in as direct support!
If we send the Eva to the surface
to intercept, it'll be too late.
Request Euro's cooperation.
Deploy Unit-02 to the Geofront.
How's Unit-00?
Making emergency repairs to the left arm.
It'll be just good enough to launch.
Send it to back up Unit-02
as soon as it's done.
Going out there alone will be dangerous.
Roger!
And Unit-01?
Currently preparing to
activate with the Dummy System.
Hurry it up!
That's in the direction of the city, right?
It'll be fine. We're headed
straight for the Geofront shelter.
Phone's aren't working, either!
Target entering the Geofront!
About to make contact with Eva Unit-02!
Do we have communications with Unit-02?
The two-way link has been cut.
Making contact from our end is...
I see.
So you want to do this alone.
It smells so good.
An Eva that smells like
someone else isn't bad, either.
It's already breached the
fifth line of defense.
If I don't get this wrapped
up quick, HQ is a goner!
Its AT field's too strong.
I won't get anywhere from this distance.
Hup.
Ho.
Hah!
Guess I'll make a go of it with this.
Let's see how you like this!
If I get it from point-blank range...
Oh, crap!
Why you little...! Talk about a toughie!
Dummy System connected.
Initiate contact.
Yes, ma'am.
What happened?
It's no use! Unit-01 won't activate!
It's refusing to accept the Dummy?
Fuyutsuki.
Take care of things for a while.
Up we go.
I won't be able to win at this rate.
All right! Guess I'll give it a try.
I'm going to see what an Eva can
do when it abandons its humanity.
Invert mode.
Backdoor code... "The Beast!"
Bear with it, Eva Unit-02.
I'll bear with it, too.
I had no idea an Eva
had such functionality!
The restrictors are being disengaged! All
readings are outside the standard range!
Unable to monitor plug interior! But...
Plug depth is likely in the negative range.
To think she's even willing
to plunge into the contamination zone...
We can't allow this! It's too dangerous!
Nothing ventured,
nothing...
gained!
Just a little more!
The Eva's bestial second form.
Even when it abandoned its humanity and
focused solely on combat, it couldn't win.
So this is the limit of our capabilities.
Unit-00?!
She doesn't even have a rifle!
Don't tell me...!
Rei, don't! Rei!
AT field at maximum!
I'll make it so Ikari...
never has to pilot the Eva again!
So, I'll...
A single Eva won't be able
to get through that AT field.
Unit-02, this is your final task!
Just one more layer!
Run, Unit-02 pilot.
Thank you.
Where's Unit-00?
This shelter has been
designated as being in an unsafe area.
Please evacuate to a safe area at once.
I repeat. This shelter...
Ow, that hurt...
I almost wound up dead there.
Oh?
What are you doing here?
I was wondering where
the other unit was. Now I know.
I...
I made up my mind not to pilot it anymore.
Questioning whether to pilot an Eva or not?
I had no idea anyone ever
agonized over something like that.
Then you should just get
out of here already.
Here, I'll help you.
I made up my mind not to pilot it.
But you know...
There's no fun in being all
twisted and sorry for yourself.
This can't be! An Angel devouring an Eva?
That's impossible!
Something's strange.
The target's ID signal is
switching over to that of Unit-00!
We've been had!
The Dogma won't self-destruct now,
even if the Angel enters!
It'll be able to get to Lilith with ease.
It's merging with Unit-00.
It assimilated the Eva, pilot and all.
You're going to end up dead, too.
Hurry up and run.
Aw, there he goes...
Above-ground HQ facilities annihilated!
Foundation 3 has suffered a direct hit!
Final armor plating has been liquefied!
No! The main shaft is completely exposed!
Is Unit-01 still not ready?
Unable to anchor plug in place!
Dummy System rejecting connection signal!
Keep going. Start over again from 308.
List 308, begin checking.
Why?
Why do you reject me, Yui?
Please let me pilot it!
Let me... Let me...
pilot Unit-01!
What are you doing here?
Dad!
I am...
the Evangelion Unit-01 pilot,
Shinji Ikari!
Target descending through
Terminal Dogma, Layer 7!
Target has passed Layer 7!
It's coming here!
Evacuate noncombatants!
Emergency evacuation of noncombatants!
I repeat. Emergency evacuation
of noncombatants! Hurry!
Eva Unit-01?!
Shinji!
Miss Misato!
Disengage all locks!
I'm out of power?
Unit-01 has reached its operational limit!
The auxiliary is down, too!
Shinji!
Give back...
Ayanami!
It's moving...?
But it's supposed to be
at its operational limit...
Has it gone berserk?
I don't know...
what in the world is
happening to Unit-01.
The Eva has powers like that?
Unit-01 is transcending
the limits of humanity?
Plug depth is over 180!
He's already in danger!
Stop this, Shinji!
You won't be able
to come back to humanity!
I don't care what happens to me.
I don't care what happens to the world.
But Ayanami...
If it's the last thing I do,
I'm saving Ayanami, no matter what!
Go, Shinji!
Misato?!
Don't do it for someone else!
Do it for the sake of
what you want yourself!
Where are you, Ayanami?!
It's no use.
I can only survive in here now.
Ayanami?!
It's okay, Ikari.
Even if I disappear,
there are replacements.
There are replacements.
You're wrong!
You're the only Ayanami there is!
So I'm going to save you now!
Oh no!
The restrictors regulating
its shape are gone!
Unable to analyze!
The Eva we had contained
with the bounds of humanity
is reclaiming its rightful shape.
Breaking free of humanity's spell,
it's transcending humanity,
turning into a nearly divine being.
Inside the huge swells of complementarity,
it's binding together the heavens, the earth,
and all creation, transforming
into an energy condensate.
Purely to grant the wish of a human being.
For that and nothing else.
Ayanami!
Come on!
They forced Unit-01 to become the catalyst
before they had their pieces in place.
Commander Ikari,
Seele isn't going to take this lying down.
I want to spread my wings
in this big open sky
Just as we had thought, between those two,
they were able to awaken Unit-01.
Yes.
We have just a little more
to go until we attain our plan.
Ayanami, thank you for
the thing with my dad.
I'm sorry, I wasn't able to do anything.
It doesn't matter now.
This is enough.
Now I see... He gets all the breaks.
I wonder if it's the
difference in smell, after all.
This is the birth of a new life form
that's grown beyond this world's Logos.
And as the price for that...
all life forms of old shall perish.
Wings...
Just like the ones 15 years ago...
Yes, the continuation
of the Second Impact...
The Third Impact is beginning!
The world is ending.
What in the world was that?!
Now, the promised time
has come, Shinji Ikari.
This time for sure,
I'll make you happy, if no one else.
Eva Unit-01 is put into suspension
with Rei and Shinji still inside.
The fortified city is scrapped.
Nerv personnel are incarcerated.
Eva Unit-06 is dropped into the Dogma.
Eva Unit-08, which
comes to life, and its pilot.
The children with destiny built
into them finally come together.
Where, oh, where will the tale of
the people who wish to live lead us?
Next Time,
"Evangelion New Theatrical Edition: Q."
Now, then, more fan
service coming next time!