(male narrator)
Last week on MasterChef...
(Christina)
Salisbury steak.
- [laughs]
- Wow.
(narrator)
When force to think
outside the box...
(Gordon)
That's the water in there.
(narrator)
Veronica...
Three compartments of it
has been filled up with puke.
(narrator)
And Jesse...
It's like
a mouthful of sand.
(narrator)
Turned their TV dinners...
Please take off your apron.
(narrator)
Into a TV disaster.
Tonight...
(Gordon)
We are all here to celebrate
the 100th episode.
(narrator)
Can the top 14 rise
to the occasion?
- Perfect.
- Whoo!
(narrator)
Or will the party...
What is this, anybody?
Oh [bleep].
(narrator)
Go up in smoke?
(Gordon)
It's a celebration.
Not a cremation.
(narrator)
60 miles from
the MasterChef kitchen,
our 14 remaining home cooks
are dropped off
in Rancho Palos Verdes,
California,
for a historic team challenge.
(Charlie)
Ocean's behind us.
There's vineyards.
Whatever we're doing,
I'm gonna enjoy.
It's gonna be a wonderful
experience.
Welcome.
Good to see you guys.
(Olivia)
I'm a California girl
through and through.
It's so refreshing
to be outdoors,
but I know
that it's kind of, like,
the silence before the storm.
Welcome to your next
big team challenge.
We are all here
to celebrate a huge milestone
for all of us
here on MasterChef.
The 100th episode.
[all cheering]
- Come on.
And guess who will be
making all the food
for this incredible celebration?
[laughter]
That's right.
You will be
making a spectacular lunch
for 100 esteemed guests.
- Yeah!
- Whoo!
- Yeah.
- [clapping]
I've been watching MasterChef
since it started.
And it's kind of nice to be
part of history.
You will all be cooking
for luminaries
of the culinary world.
Restaurateurs, chefs,
food critics,
even former contestants
who have gone on to success
in our industry.
Now, for this incredible
occasion,
we want to see one amazing
appetizer
and one stunning entree
from each team.
For your appetizer,
we want each team to make a dish
featuring these beauties.
- [cheering]
- Exquisite Malpeque oysters
with the most amazing
Royal Ossetra caviar.
- Whoo!
- Now, we also want you to make
a elegant entree starring this.
[light cheering and applause]
(Gordon)
A phenomenal duck breast.
Your food must rise
to the occasion.
(all)
Yes, Chef.
Nick and Olivia,
you had the winning dishes
in the previous challenge, so
you will become team captains.
(Nick)
100th episode.
History in the making.
There is nothing
more important
than winning
this team challenge.
Now, Nick, since you had
the winning dish,
you get to pick first.
First person I'm gonna pick
is probably the hardest worker
in the kitchen.
Amanda.
(Gordon)
Amanda. Wow.
[clapping]
Nick, who I see
as the best contestant here,
picks me first,
and I am absolutely honored,
and I feel so good.
Okay, Olivia, next.
The reason I'm going to
choose this person is because
I think they have demonstrated
a lot of technique.
Derrick.
(Gordon)
Excellent.
Derrick, come up.
My worry with Olivia is
I don't think she's confident
enough in herself
to be a team captain.
We've been on a winning team
together twice
and we're gonna make it
a third time with Stephen.
(Gordon)
Wow.
Katrina.
Sara.
Chris.
I'm picking Charlie.
- I'm gonna choose Hetal.
- Hetal, welcome.
- I'm taking Shelly.
- Shelly. Good.
I'm gonna choose Kerry.
[lively music]
Tommy, Claudia,
final pick.
How do you feel?
It feels like being
in grade school again,
when I'd be the last one to get
picked for the softball team.
I've worked with Nick before,
and we've both worked
together seamlessly,
and I'm hoping that Nick
is gonna pick me.
I wanna win.
So I'm picking the best person
that's gonna that's gonna
fit with my team.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
It's gonna be Claudia.
(Gordon)
Wow. Claudia.
[light applause]
Tommy, please come pick up
your apron.
[light applause]
I'm worried about
having Tommy on my team.
He does stupid things
under pressure.
He overcomplicates
and he's not the greatest at
working as a team.
Right. Red Team, Blue Team,
you have just 60 minutes
before you'll be serving
that stunning oyster and caviar
appetizer to our
100 esteemed guests.
50 appetizers,
50 entrees for each team.
Are you ready?
(all)
Yes, Chef.
Your 60 minutes prep
starts now.
Off you go, guys.
(narrator)
The pressure is on.
With the pantry stocked
full of the finest ingredients,
it is now up to our home cooks
to devise and execute a menu
worthy of the MasterChef
100th episode celebration.
What I'm thinking
is a poached oyster.
- Yeah.
- In white wine and butter.
- I like it.
- We're gonna sit it
on top of a pickled slaw.
I make a salsa with, like,
jalapeño, apple, and kumquats.
- And I saw kumquats back there.
- Cool, instead of kumquats,
- put cucumbers.
- Okay. Put cucumbers. Love it.
We'll put you in charge of that.
You want to make
a little crème fraiche?
Mix the caviar inside.
It's gonna go good
with the apple salad.
- It will have it already--
- I like the crème fraiche.
You know, I'm feeling really
good about this menu.
It's a great collaboration
with Nick.
Okay, for the duck, I'm thinking
a Moroccan type of spiced duck.
And then candied carrots.
- Beautiful?
- Yeah.
- Good?
- Okay. Let's go.
(narrator)
While the Blue Team
quickly agrees on
a simple, upscale menu,
on the Red Team,
Captain Olivia has more
ambitious plans in mind.
We're gonna
smoke the oyster.
We can fry this oyster
and make it really good.
It fries super quick.
I think it's the fastest way
- to go with the oyster.
- I wanna smoke the oyster.
They're gonna do
something expected.
If I may recommend,
shaved cucumber
'cause it's bright and light.
(Olivia)
Done, but I want
a citrus in there.
Use a vinaigrette?
(Olivia)
Yes, perfect.
I have another challenge today:
working with Olivia.
And she's coming up
with the menu.
[mocking Olivia]
It's like so many components.
We're gonna do duck basted
in orange and fresh ginger.
When that comes out,
you supreme the orange,
add the orange, and then
we're gonna toast pistachios.
We're gonna do
a cauliflower purée.
It's gonna go along with carrots
that are roasted with
cumin and onion.
(Katrina)
I think it's too many
ingredients.
- I do too.
- Too many ingredients?
- Yup.
- [sighs]
It's too complicated
for all of us to nail this.
- Yeah, I'm sorry guys.
- Okay.
- We can do it.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
(narrator)
As the teams begin their prep,
out in the dining area,
100 VIP guests are arriving.
Chefs, food critics,
and past contestants gather
to celebrate the 100th episode
of MasterChef.
I hope these guys are
bringing their A-game.
Make sure it is good.
When it goes on that plate,
you only get one shot
to impress.
This is it.
We need to get these roasting
right now.
♪ ♪
First of all, the milestone
of 100 episodes
of one of the biggest
cooking competitions
anywhere in the world,
think about it.
Extraordinary.
There we go.
That's the flavor we need.
I am very nervous.
Your reputation, yours,
and mine,
and MasterChef's reputation
is on the line here.
(Christopher)
You want me to start
smoking oysters now?
Smoke it and chill it,
then we can start now.
- Absolutely.
- We're giving them
these beautiful ingredients
to work with.
Can they
execute beautiful appetizers
and beautiful entrees?
The bit of advice I would
have to give to them today
is just don't overthink it.
You've got great ingredients
to work with.
Just give them respect,
and your dish will shine.
Oh.
Oh, that smoke.
Yeah, sorry, it's smoky.
(Derrick)
How long does it take to
smoke the oyster?
(Christopher)
Six minutes.
No. Not six minutes,
that's an overcooked oyster.
(Tommy)
They just have to be
touched by smoke.
It has to be cooked.
Not raw.
Oh, my God.
(Tommy)
Being Creole,
I know my way around oysters.
I know oysters cooked, grilled,
raw, flambéed,
in Thanksgiving stuffing.
But they're not listening to me.
- What are you doing there?
- Smoking oysters.
[dramatic music]
But they're [bleep].
(Gordon)
Olivia.
- Are they overcooked?
- They're [bleep].
They're all overcooked.
- Did you test one?
- No, sir.
You don't throw all the oysters
in there and cook them all.
They're all [bleep].
I hate to say it,
but I told you.
I told you.
Guys, what are we gonna do?
I've got no more oysters.
♪ ♪
You don't throw all the oysters
in there and cook them all.
They're all--
guys, what are we gonna do?
I've got no more oysters.
Chris takes the oysters and...
[laughs softly]
Incinerates them.
Are all the oysters in?
(both)
No.
Come on, guys.
Can you have a meeting
and sort this out?
- Yeah.
- Now.
Thank you.
Okay, guys.
Group decision.
Do we wanna serve two oysters?
The consequence of
ruining these oysters means that
we have to put out
two on each plate
instead of three.
I mean, for me,
that feels ridiculous.
So everything else we do
has to be that much better
to make up for the fact that
we don't have a good enough
portion size for everyone.
Are they going to change course?
[sighs]
They got to step up now.
(Gordon)
I'm seriously worried.
(narrator)
With just minutes before
the start of service
for the 100th episode lunch,
the judges check on
the Red Team's oyster appetizer.
Okay, Olivia, let's go.
Uh...right.
Where's the appetizer?
- What is that?
- Right here.
No, are you taking the piss
or what?
- Uh-uh.
- No.
That is the appetizer?
- Yeah.
- Where's the caviar?
Are you serious?
That should be the garnish
on top of another dish.
(Tommy)
I have never been
more embarrassed.
What we wind up with is really
an amuse-bouch this big.
(Gordon)
Sorry, not good enough.
Let's go. Take that back, guys.
Change that.
Just over five minutes
from now we're open.
Let's go.
Oh, my God.
My expectations are
through the roof right now,
simply because it's
the 100th episode of MasterChef.
I don't know how much higher
the standard can be held.
I would be very nervous
right now.
- Okay, so use that dressing.
- So, start--
Start using the dressing.
Mandoline the fennel.
One minute to go.
Right behind you,
right behind you.
- Go, go.
- You got it, Nick.
Come on, guys.
Come on, Blue Team.
- You got it.
- You good. You good
I'm looking around
at my Blue Team.
Everybody's at their stations.
Let's keep 'em rolling, guys.
We're doing well.
(Nick)
Everyone's doing
what needs to be done.
We keep rolling like this,
and the Red Team
might as well
jump off that cliff.
Red Team, Blue Team,
we are ready to start serving.
Let's go.
We're ready for service
on table one.
- Red Team!
- Yes?
- Yes.
- Get a plan.
Figure this out.
Blue Team's going out
with their food.
Table six, please.
(narrator)
The Blue Team is serving
butter poached oysters
with cucumber and apple pickle
and caviar vinaigrette.
Meanwhile, the Red Team
is still working on
their newly revised appetizer.
Smoked oysters and caviar with a
salad of fennel and grapefruit.
You guys, work from one
direction to the other.
- So which way are we going?
- Let's go.
- So when she's doing a step...
- Okay, that's good. Good.
You're following
with the next.
- Got it? Okay.
- I know--I'm--this is like--
She's doing the caviar
behind me.
I set all the plates out,
and Olivia starts
going scattered.
You've got to work
from one way or another.
- I know, I know.
- This is confusing.
The clock is ticking and we got
to get that food going out.
Eight covers
for an oyster salad.
- We have the oysters, Derrick.
- No.
I'm talking about
the next table.
- Okay.
- I understand what I'm calling,
- okay?
- Okay.
Derrick is an alpha male,
and we gets a chance,
he's going to push Olivia
straight to the side
and take over,
like he always does.
(Derrick)
Guys, faster.
We got to push.
Ugh.
Service, please.
(narrator)
With Derrick
helping to expedite,
the Red Team finally
gets their appetizers out.
This isn't what I expected.
- Yeah, I know.
- I was expecting, like,
something a little bit more
like a bite.
- Yeah.
- And this is more like a salad.
(narrator)
In today's challenge,
each team will serve 50
of the 100 VIPs,
whose feedback will help
the judges decide
which team performed the best,
and which team will have to
face the pressure test.
So, this is probably
the table
everyone was most nervous
to cook for.
[laughter]
Tell me what we thought about
the Blue Team's oyster course.
I think that they were creative
with the plating.
It was colorful.
I don't think
the caviar should've been
sitting on the plate.
I wish it were on top of
the actual dish itself.
I think my plate
explains it all.
Blue Team's oysters
were delicious.
All right.
Thank you, guys.
I loved the concept of the dish
with a lot of
contrasting flavors.
But I would have loved
to have
more oysters and caviar
on the dish.
Service, please.
Last table for appetizers.
- Olivia, two seconds.
- Yeah?
Yes, Chef.
So that was terrible.
- Okay? That wasn't good.
- Okay.
(Gordon)
The problem is,
there's no organization.
You need to be in control
of your brigade.
I know, but Derrick seems to
think that I can't handle it,
so he's just [bleep] me off,
which is really
becoming a problem.
Well...put him in his place.
Okay.
- You're the captain.
- Okay.
So, at the end of the day,
this is riding on
your shoulders.
- I'm sorry, that's just it.
- No, you're right.
You've got a whole other course
to claw this back.
- You're right.
- Okay?
Get a meeting,
get your team together,
and they do as you say.
- Okay.
- Period.
- You're right. Yeah.
- Got it?
- Thank you. Thank you.
- Let's go. Come on.
Gordon basically gave me
a slap in the face.
I'm like, Olivia,
trust yourself.
You know what you're doing.
No time for tears.
I have five minutes
to turn it around.
Red Team, Blue Team,
just under five minutes
for 50 stunning entrees.
Let's go.
[exciting music]
Purée, carrots, duck,
garnishes, sauce over here.
♪ ♪
(Stephen)
I got something burning
back here.
It smells like plas--
Plastic?
[dramatic music]
[bleep].
♪ ♪
Blue Team, what is this?
- Golly.
- What?
♪ ♪
Blue Team, anybody?
That's my fault.
Set the [bleep] timer.
I gave Charlie one job.
How do you burn carrots?
Unbelievable.
(Nick)
We don't have anymore carrots?
(Amanda)
No.
So we need another veg.
That was our veg,
so I don't know what to do.
That's not good.
Charlie, it's a celebration.
Not a cremation.
[bleep].
Happy birthday 100, MasterChef!
[cheering]
(narrator)
It's the celebration lunch
for the 100th episode
of MasterChef.
While Christina adds
finishing touches
to her own celebration cake,
the entree service
is in full-swing.
24 customers still to cook for.
- Come on, Blue Team!
- We can do it.
- Charlie, you got duck?
- It's coming.
(narrator)
The Blue Team is serving
seared Moroccan spiced duck
with forbidden rice
and roasted fennel.
We need six more duck.
Copy that.
(narrator)
The Red Team is serving duck
braised in ginger
and orange butter
with cauliflower purée, roasted
carrots, and cilantro oil.
Don't do too many
'cause we don't it to get cold.
Even though we got off
to a rough start,
I am so confident in the fact
that we have turned it around.
Nice plates, guys.
I know we're putting out
something that looks really good
and it tastes amazing.
You're doing awesome expoing.
Plates look beautiful.
I would want to be
on this team right now.
- Good job.
- Thank you, Chef.
- Whoo!
(narrator)
While the Red Team has found
their rhythm,
on the Blue Team, timing issues
are slowing down their service.
This duck is cold.
- Duck is what?
- It's cold.
Excuse me?
The duck is cold.
Who sent me the duck?
- Charlie, did you give--
- I did not--
I did not bring the duck
up there.
Nick brought the duck up there,
Chef.
Nick brought the duck.
Come on then, Nick.
Talk to the team, Nick.
I'm talking to 'em.
(Nick)
It's chaos.
Utter chaos.
Charlie's cutting duck
and leaving it out
to sit and get cold.
I've got a sauce
that's burning over here.
Oh, come on.
(Nick)
Then I put Shelly on the sauce.
It's ruined.
I got the sauce.
Go.
We started out so strong.
I don't understand
where we're going right now.
Charlie, we need
one, two, three.
Now.
Three.
Don't slice too early, Charlie.
(Shelly)
You got to let them rest.
Chef Ramsay's telling me
let the duck rest.
Charlie, now.
It needs to rest
before I cut it.
It's just gonna bleed.
Now, Charlie.
Just do it now.
But the captain of the team
is telling me
cut the duck
and put it on a plate.
So I cut the duck
because he's the captain.
(Gordon)
Are they cooked?
Oh, my God.
Nick.
Give me that duck.
You can't slice that
when it's that raw.
Nick is the worst leader ever.
(Gordon)
Team, come here.
Urgently.
Everybody's walking around
like they're on holiday,
in a vineyard,
picking [bleep] grapes.
Have some respect,
get your team up to speed,
and start getting some quality.
Please.
(narrator)
While Nick tries to get
his Blue Team back on track,
out in the dining area,
Christina discovers
that the Red Team
is also having problems
with the cook on their duck.
- It's overcooked for you?
- Yeah.
(woman)
Okay.
Yeah.
In today's challenge,
comments from the VIPs
will be crucial in helping the
judges to determine a winner.
The losing team will
face the pressure test.
I had the Blue Team's today.
It was pretty remarkable.
Overall, I give it
an eight out of ten.
(Gordon)
Last table, Blue Team.
Are you happy with that, Nick?
- Yes, sir. Yes, Chef.
- Good. Six top. Let's go.
- What table number?
- Table four, please.
Overall, I think Blue Team
did a great job.
Just inconsistent with the duck,
but other than that I loved it.
(Graham)
Last table.
Take it, take it, take it.
I think the Red Team rocked it.
The duck was cooked
to a beautiful temperature,
and the roasted carrots were
a huge hit at the table.
Whoo!
I don't know if we've won.
I don't know if we've lost,
because you never know.
But, ultimately,
I had a personal win.
Our duck tasted good.
Our appetizers went out on time.
We finished.
We executed.
Every single plate
looked the same.
Cook's done.
[sighs]
I wish I felt as good as I did
during appetizer round.
But at the same time,
this is my third team challenge.
I know that just because
it was hard for us
doesn't mean it was easy
for the Red Team.
[cheers and applause]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
(Gordon)
That looks incredible.
Look at that.
[cheers and applause]
- Great job.
- Thank you.
Really good job.
Amazing.
So guys, I want to introduce you
to the incredible home cooks
that, right now,
are currently experiencing
their own MasterChef journey.
(Graham)
Ladies and gentlemen,
the Red Team.
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
I've never felt such a sense
of team accomplishment.
Getting to cook
for these restaurateurs
and past contestants,
this is why I'm here.
Wow.
What an amazing thing.
Come on, guys.
The Blue Team.
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you for joining us here
to help celebrate
this 100th episode.
[cheers and applause]
Both teams had their
ups and downs,
but there can only be
one winning team.
The winning team,
who will not be facing
the dreaded pressure test...
that team
will be decided back in
the MasterChef kitchen.
- Aww!
- Come on!
To the 100th episode,
congratulations.
Well done.
[cheers and applause]
(Claudia)
The Blue Team has to win.
I cannot face
another pressure test.
So, I'm just hoping
that the Red Team screwed up
more than we did.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
(Olivia)
I've been in every
pressure test.
elimination challenge.
Like, I think this is my time
to be the winner.
Welcome back to
the MasterChef kitchen.
In yesterday's challenge,
we asked you to help us
celebrate the 100th episode
of MasterChef.
Red Team, captained by Olivia,
scared us.
Christina, Graham,
and myself were shocked
by that appetizer.
It looked like half a canapé.
You know that.
But you bounced back,
you made decisions,
you stuck to them, and you
finally got over the line.
Blue Team, captained by Nick.
Wow. You presented
that first appetizer
and it made us take a step back.
You nailed it.
Unfortunately, you didn't
maintain that standard
through the entire service.
The team that we decided
gave the best performance
and ultimately put out
the best plates,
the team safe
from elimination...
Red Team.
(Katrina)
Yeah!
[upbeat music]
(Christina)
Congratulations, Red Team.
Your journey in the MasterChef
kitchen continues,
so you're gonna make it
to episode 101.
- Yeah!
- Whoo!
- Good job, guys.
- [laughs]
Please, head on up.
Right now,
I'm feeling disappointed
in myself and being the team
captain of the losing team.
This is a tough loss.
I'm used to being a winner,
so this is a new flavor
for me to taste.
Blue Team, not all of you
are going to have to
face this pressure test.
Just six of you are.
[bleep].
The decision of
which member of your team
will not face the pressure test
will be made by...
all of you.
[dramatic music]
You will have five minutes
to work out a unanimous decision
amongst yourselves.
When that time is up,
we need one name.
If you cannot reach a decision,
we will eliminate
all of you.
Blue Team, not all of you
are going to have to
face this pressure test.
Just six of you are.
[bleep].
You'll have five minutes
to work out a unanimous decision
amongst yourselves.
When that time is up,
we need one name.
If you cannot reach a decision,
we will eliminate
all of you.
- Oh.
- [whistles]
Please had to the wine room
and come back with one name.
[dramatic music]
We didn't come together
in our team challenge,
so how are we gonna
come together in five minutes?
♪ ♪
We should maybe all
just say a name.
And then go from there.
- Sara.
- Charlie.
But I did everything
I was told.
Shelly burnt the sauce.
Charlie burnt the carrots.
So if you think that performance
is worthy of saving yourself,
something's wrong.
From me being able to--
watching everything,
- my vote is Stephen.
- I didn't make a mistake.
Who did I ask to do the rice?
Stephen, but Stephen knew how to
operate the pressure cooker--
- Who did I ask to do the rice?
- You asked me to.
- But when I don't know how to--
- And then I asked you to do
the sauce and you didn't know
how to do the sauce.
Shelly lives in
a whole another galaxy, man.
I don't know what
she sees in herself,
but the general consensus
of the team
is that Shelly dropped the ball.
(Graham)
Two minutes left.
Just being
absolutely objective...
- Mm-hmm.
I did help recover
on the vegetable,
the rice, the sauce.
But if I do go in
the pressure test, I'll survive.
So who are you going with?
Who are we saving, Shelly?
- I'm gonna fight for myself.
- [groans]
- How do--
- I don't wanna be down there.
Then let's all get
[bleep] eliminated.
Time.
Let's go.
Let's go, guys.
Line up please.
Thank you.
[dramatic music]
Would the person
that will not be
facing tonight's
pressure test
please step forward now?
♪ ♪
Really?
Stephen, you are officially
safe from elimination.
Please head up to the balcony.
I'm a competitor and I know
this is a competition,
but Stephen worked his ass off.
He kept the team on track and
he really deserved to be saved.
Yesterday, I presented my
world-famous birthday cake.
For this challenge tonight,
we want each of you
to present us with
something like this.
♪ ♪
Birthday cake.
Beautiful, right?
- Mm.
- Mm-hmm.
In case you're wondering
why there are two candles,
that's because,
after this pressure test,
two of your MasterChef dreams
will be...
♪ ♪
Blown out.
- Oh, my.
- Oh, God.
Now, every great birthday cake
has its own unique style.
♪ ♪
- [whistles]
- Whoo!
- Mmm, mmm, mmm.
- Yes.
You can whatever flavor
combinations you like,
as long as your cake is
a minimum of three layers,
has a beautiful frosting,
and it needs to somehow
celebrate the 100th episode.
Right. All of you, it's time
to head to your stations.
Let's go.
♪ ♪
This is the most important cake
that I've ever baked in my life.
I do not want to go back to
fixing people's air conditioner
as an A/C man in New Orleans.
Like, I got to
make this thing happen.
In front of you, you all have
everything you need to make us
an amazing birthday cake.
You also have access
to a limited pantry
to help make your cake stand out
from the crowd.
Your 90 minutes
starts...now.
(all)
Whoo!
- Come on, guys.
- Good, guys.
♪ ♪
All right, Christina,
90 minutes.
- Where would you start?
- Okay, first thing's first.
You got to get
that sponge batter going.
You start with butter, sugar,
you add your eggs one by one.
If you add eggs
too many at a time,
you will separate
your butter sugar mixture
and it will take you
three times as long
trying to get that mixture
together.
This ain't right.
(Christina)
I'd say if they don't have
their cake in the oven baking
in the first 20 minutes, they're
really starting to fall behind.
♪ ♪
I'm doing a basic sponge cake,
but it's gonna have
orange zest frosting
with toasted coconut
on the outside.
I'ma keep it kind of traditional
and I'ma do a vanilla birthday
cake with sprinkles.
I'ma make it real fun.
I'ma dress it up.
I'm making a vanilla cake with
Nutella and strawberry filling.
I've made this cake for myself
on my birthday,
so this is...a piece of cake.
20 minutes down.
Your cakes need to be
in the oven.
♪ ♪
Boom.
All right, Claudia,
tell me about the cake.
I am going to be making
a tres leches cake
with fresh fruit in the middle
exactly like those
made in Mexico.
- Good luck.
- Feliz cumpleaños,
- Señor Ramsay.
- It's not my 100th birthday.
I'm 48. Not yet.
55 minutes to get in there.
- Thank you.
- Let's go.
What is Charlie doing?
(Tommy)
He's making more batter.
He doesn't have enough batter
in his mix.
He's not gonna have a done cake.
Um...
Charlie, get your sponges
in the oven.
- I'm coming.
- And I mean quick.
Yes, sir.
46 minutes to go, guys.
Those cakes better be
out of the oven, cooling.
♪ ♪
- Ugh.
- Oh, no.
It collapsed.
♪ ♪
I think Amanda's cake's
raw in the middle.
- No.
- They have sunk to oblivion.
Oh, her cakes fell
in the middle.
(Gordon)
Oh, my goodness, me.
Yeah. I know.
I failed. I failed.
Oh, Amanda.
Amanda, Amanda, Amanda.
- What is she doing?
- Oh, Amanda.
- That's raw.
- I know.
[sighs]
I think that we're witnessing
the moment right now
where we lose
one of our favorites.
I decided to take the cakes
out of the oven too early,
and I failed
the baking challenge.
This sucks.
[crying]
♪ ♪
Oh, my goodness, me.
- That's raw.
- I know.
[sighs]
- What is she doing?
- Oh, Amanda.
Come on.
Hey, you can put this together.
Use your frosting
and your icing to patch it up.
- Yes.
- Okay?
- That's what I'm gonna do.
- And just treat it
like a bit of plastic surgery.
- Okay.
- Okay? We're in L.A.
- I'll do that.
- Look at my face.
Look at me.
You can do this.
- Thank you, Chef.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
All right, guys.
Just 17 minutes left.
(Charlie)
Whoo.
[dramatic music]
- Hi, Charlie.
- Hello.
Is your cake out of the oven?
- I'm about to.
- You're cutting it close.
- Charlie.
- You have to make a minimum
three-layer layer cake.
How are you going to
get that done?
I'm going to use this
to make a mini-birthday cake
for you.
- That's my only option.
- So how are you still
gonna get three?
You have less than
20 minutes to go.
Remember, it's got to
look pretty.
- Yes, Chef, I got you.
- Celebratory for us.
- You're gonna love this cake.
- Okay? The big 100.
- Y'all gonna love it.
- Not a lot of time.
Hit it, Charlie.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Ladies and gentlemen,
ten minutes remaining.
♪ ♪
I'm excited about Shelly's.
I think everyone's sticking
to their roots,
and she's going with
kind of an island theme.
She's got, you know,
the rum and the mint.
Claudia's doing
a tres leches cake,
so finally she's playing
to her strength.
(Christina)
You got it, Claudia.
Just under three minutes to go.
(Gordon)
This is where
you have an opportunity
to make your cake shine.
♪ ♪
It's too hot.
- What is he doing?
- He's using his hand.
- What is that?
- [laughs]
The human spatula.
Oh, my God, Charlie.
I can't even--
I don't wanna look at this.
- Put it on the pan.
- Leave it on the pan.
- Oh, my God.
- [laughs]
Ten, nine, eight, seven...
(Christina)
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
(judges)
Six, five, four,
three, two, one.
(Gordon)
And stop.
Hands in the air.
[cheers and applause]
Now that's what I call pressure.
Well done.
Please bring your birthday cakes
down to the front.
[suspenseful music]
Sadly, two out of the six of you
will be leaving shortly.
I'll begin with Nick.
Christina's probably
the best baker in the world,
so I'm nervous for her
to taste my cake.
But after looking down to my
left, I think I'm fine.
What kind of cake
did you make?
I made a sponge cake
with a mascarpone
and blood orange icing.
- Okay.
- And toasted coconut.
Well, let's see how it tastes.
The knife is slicing
very easily down and through.
♪ ♪
Looks pretty good.
[Nick clears throat]
♪ ♪
Your frosting is sweet
and definitely has
the essence of orange.
A little orange juice, a little
orange zest in the cake batter,
I think, would've helped
reinforce the flavor.
But, overall,
I am pretty impressed.
Thank you.
[suspenseful music]
Amanda, go ahead and tell me
what you've made.
(Amanda)
I made a vanilla sponge cake
with a Nutella, butter cream,
and strawberry filling,
and butter cream outside.
♪ ♪
The center, clearly not done.
It's delicious, though.
The frosting's not grainy.
Filling's great.
Strawberry's are done perfectly.
Just, what a shame...
- Yeah.
- That the cake itself,
which is what everything
is built upon,
is not cooked.
But based on the flavor,
I would say
that you're not out of it yet.
Thank you.
[exhales]
♪ ♪
Shelly, describe
your cake, please.
(Shelly)
It's a mojito rum cake with
lime zest and some spiced rum.
♪ ♪
Unfortunately,
your sponge is undercooked.
So this solidified dampness
is where the cake was liquid,
and it's gotten all firm.
♪ ♪
It needs more cooking, Shelly.
Is that your best performance?
Sadly not.
Thank you.
♪ ♪
Sara.
(Sara)
I made a yellow sponge
and then there is
a raspberry sauce inside.
♪ ♪
It's nice, soft, even,
in that slicing process.
♪ ♪
The cream cheese
frosting tastes more
just like butter
confection sugar
than it does sort of, like,
that rich, creamy cream cheese.
I think that the raspberry
was a smart decision.
But you're on the same playing
field as everyone else.
Okay.
♪ ♪
All right, Claudia.
Let's discuss
what we have first.
I've made for you a traditional
tres leches cake
with a lemon cream cheese
frosting.
So tres leches,
what milks are you using?
What's in this?
I used sweetened condensed milk,
evaporated milk, and whole milk.
♪ ♪
Dang.
[laughs]
(both)
Wow.
See how even the layers are
and everything?
I mean, you should be proud.
That's pretty awesome.
♪ ♪
That's delicious.
Yeah, it's everything
we're looking for.
- Thank you so much, Chef.
- Good job.
(both)
Thank you.
- Yeah, Claud!
- Good job.
- [all cheering]
- I knew it.
(Katrina)
Good job.
[clapping]
♪ ♪
Charlie, our 100th birthday
celebration.
The idea tonight was to bake us
a stunning cake.
- All right.
- It looks like you've been
frosting a lump of concrete.
- But it tastes good.
(Charlie)
Yes, Chef.
Happy Birthday, MasterChef.
I mean, are you serious?
♪ ♪
The idea tonight was to
bake us a stunning cake.
All right.
Describe your mess.
What I've created
for you is a wonderful
three-layer sponge cake
with sprinkles in the sponge
and blood orange icing.
And this is really good.
It would be good
if I was [bleep] blind.
[laughter]
You could cover.
[laughs]
It tastes really good though,
Chef.
I promise you.
Okay.
Well...
It's pretty.
[laughter]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Claudia, taste that,
will you, please?
♪ ♪
Oh, my God.
It's delicious.
[laughter]
It's good?
[laughs]
Come on.
Don't leave me hanging.
I mean, the sponge is fragrant,
the frosting's delicious,
but you have to have
the ugliest cake tonight.
Not just in
the MasterChef kitchen.
I'm talking America.
[laughter]
I'm sorry about that.
Wow.
[suspenseful music]
(Graham)
That was a tough pressure test.
Please come around front.
I'm so disappointed in myself.
I feel like I have one foot
on my way back to Brooklyn.
Two of you will be going home.
But there was one of you that
put together a birthday cake
that we were
really excited about.
Claudia.
- [all cheering]
- Good job.
Go ahead and head upstairs.
Whoo!
I cannot believe it.
Amanda and Sara are known to be
the best bakers
in our competition,
and they've just been
knocked down by the Latina.
Excuse me?
Like--
exc--I'm sorry, Graham,
can you just repeat that again?
- You did great.
- Thank you.
Can the following two home cooks
please step forward?
Nick and Sara.
Your cakes were on
the same level.
Not good enough to be
put on display at a bakery,
but, to be honest,
not bad enough
to eliminate you this evening.
Both of you can head on up
to the balcony.
You are safe tonight.
Thank you.
[applause]
♪ ♪
Amanda, you know,
needed more cooking,
great intention, but you can't
re-cook a sponge.
Shelly,
it presented itself well,
but too dense.
And the density was caused
because it was undercooked.
Charlie wears his heart
on his sleeve
every time he comes into
this kitchen.
But you managed
to put something together
that didn't really look
like a layered cake.
It looked like an accident.
Charlie, step forward please.
Your time is done
in the MasterChef kitchen.
- Oh, God.
- Please take off your apron
and put it onto your bench.
- Bye, sweetie.
- Bye.
You all right?
All right.
Good-bye, y'all.
- Charlie!
- Bye, Charlie.
- We love you.
- We love you!
[applause]
[upbeat music]
I came in here
straight from New Orleans.
An attic rat,
fixing old air conditioners.
Who that?
And I'm leaving here
a well-tuned chef.
I feel like
I'm really a chef now.
Red Team!
[cheers and laughter]
This is the beginning of
a lot of good things.
This opens up so many
other doors for me
to continue in
the culinary world.
- At a boy, Charlie.
- I'm nowhere near done
with cooking.
♪ ♪
Amanda and Shelly,
this is so hard.
[somber music]
[sighs]
[whispering]
♪ ♪
I'm hoping that
I've done enough to my cake
for the flavors to be there
and that I won't go home.
♪ ♪
[whispering]
I'm so close to changing my life
for my little girl.
And I have so much more to give
in this kitchen.
And I don't wanna go home today.
Amanda and Shelly, two very
strong and talented cooks.
I don't enjoy
sending talent home.
So this isn't easy.
Shelly...
Please take your apron off.
Say goodnight to Amanda.
Give me a kiss.
Come on.
♪ ♪
- It was a pleasure.
- I'm sorry.
It was a pleasure.
You understand me?
I promise you.
And head upstairs
to the balcony.
What?
(Gordon)
Take your apron off and
head upstairs to the balcony.
♪ ♪
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
♪ ♪
[crying]
It's okay.
♪ ♪
[Shelly crying]
Amanda, I think everybody
in this kitchen
had such high hopes for you.
You cook brilliantly.
You mustn't let this become
the end of your journey.
Come here, gorgeous.
- Amanda, good job.
- Oh, thank you so much.
- Love you, Amanda.
- Thanks, guys.
- We love you, Amanda.
- Love you.
[applause]
For me to be at MasterChef
has been incredible.
[cheering]
I'm absolutely proud of myself
for breaking the stereotypes
that are out there.
I am strong.
I'm confident.
Enjoy.
I'm Muslim.
I'm not suppressed.
I have my own voice.
And I had three of the best
chefs in the entire world
eat my food
and say great things.
(Graham)
You're nailing it
with the presentation,
the flavors, and the technique,
which is what we're looking for.
You are back
with a vengeance.
- Great job.
- Thank you so much, Chef.
(Gordon)
The Red Team.
[cheering]
I'm gonna continue cooking.
I'm gonna continue baking.
And I can't wait to see
who the next MasterChef is.
[upbeat music]
(narrator)
Next week, on MasterChef...
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
(narrator)
The home cooks...
(Gordon)
Let's go, let's go.
(narrator)
Are faced with replicating
Gordon Ramsay's greatest hits.
- Whoo.
- [laughs]
This is going to be impossible.
(Olivia)
I have no idea how to do this.
(narrator)
It's the toughest culinary
challenge of their lives.
- Aah!
- Ow, you're so hot.
- Come on, come on.
- Oh, my God.
Oh.
(narrator)
Some home cooks reach
new heights...
That, I want to run
back to Vegas with.
(narrator)
And others crash
to an all-time low.
(Christina)
You wanted us to taste this?
[dramatic music]