As a doctor, you spend
about a third of your nights
sleeping at the hospital,
but in truth,
not a lot of sleeping takes place.
- Dr Reid.
- I'm not sucking my thumb.
Mr Rodriguez is coding.
- You look pretty.
- Thank you.
You learn to appreciate
the little things,
like waking up in your own bed.
Of course, if there's someone
there with you...
- Sorry I woke you.
- I'll live.
...that's just gravy.
Yep, there's nothing
like mornings at home.
- Hey, there, sunshine.
- Morning.
I forgot Carla
is staying with us
while her building
is being fumigated.
Hey, don't use Rowdy to cover up
your giblets. Apologize.
Tell me why we have no milk
or orange juice,
but, like, 40 fruit cups in here?
The average resident
owes over $ 100,000
in med school loans and makes
about as much as a waiter.
So you have to do things
to make ends meet.
Like you can cover
someone's shift.
Or you can steal stuff
from the hospital.
Or you can moonlight
at an urgent care centre.
Or you can steal stuff.
Or your dad
can pay for everything.
Or... Well, you know.
- Is it clear?
- Come on, come on.
Go! Go! Run!
- Hold up.
- Why?
There's been several thefts.
We're doing bag checks.
What about that guy
taking scrubs?
Hey, Tom.
He doesn't have a bag.
Go ahead, narc. I'm clean.
Yeah?
Of course,
if he was checking my trunk...
- Pudding. Score!
- Come on! Let's go, let's go!
Get me a butterscotch, buddy.
Come on!
I did that cardioversion,
I extubated Mrs Bays,
and I finished
all the transfer summaries
- on the nursing-home patients.
- Well, what can I say?
You did exceptional work today,
Newbie, and I'm proud of you.
Did he just wink at me?
- Is there a problem?
- I'm just so happy.
- No, no problem, sir.
- Attaboy.
And, Laverne,
what is that delightfully
naught-ay scent you're wearing?
It's called Twelve-Hour Shift.
- Yeah, it is.
- Why the hell is he so cheery?
Because I did
exceptional work today.
Hey, babe.
I ordered the fight on pay-per-view,
got a six-pack of beer.
- We are leaving this second.
- Hop on, Blondie. Come here.
Oh, Perry gonna get
some loving
Perry gonna get some loving
Oh, Perry gonna get some...
Is there one bathroom
in this damn place
that has toilet paper,
or do I have to start
carrying around
a basket of leaves?
This is the reason why
your headache didn't go away.
That's actually pronounced
analgesic, not "anal"-gesic.
Sir, the pills go in your mouth.
We're going to be short
a doctor tomorrow,
so if you've got a friend
that wants an extra 300 bucks...
And they said they'll pay you
200 bucks. Cash money.
Sweet! Dude, you are
like the best friend ever.
Hell, yeah.
My mother
lives with me all year.
My Aunt has to take care of her
for one week
and she won't stop bitching.
My dad's coming in to town
for a conference tomorrow.
- You don't seem stressed out.
- I haven't pooed in six days.
Twice this morning,
and I haven't even had my coffee yet.
You really pick odd things
to brag about.
I'm just saying,
if I had to get three by lunch,
I probably could.
Hey, guys.
Gyno Girls, twelve o'clock.
Obstetrics and Gynaecology
is a specialty
that's usually
dominated by women.
Dr Reid, I'm Dr Gerson.
We were just wondering
if you have any thoughts
about your specialty,
because we really think
you're OB/GYN material.
Being a Gyno Girl
is a lot like being in a sorority.
JD, I can't go with Dr Gerson
because I have to help you, right?
Give me a second. I'm figuring
something out for a patient.
I'm glad we all finally
experimented with each other,
but I'll never do it again.
Dammit.
- Julie!
- Hey, Rob! Good to see you.
Hey, Dan!
God, I just hate that every doctor
you ever gave a drug sample to
sniffs around you
like a little puppy dog.
I never gave those guys anything.
I slept with them.
Great.
Those Gyno Girls
are putting the pressure on.
We must have looked
at a hundred women's bajingos today.
Bajingo, bajingo, bajingo.
I mean, I can't even look
at my own bajingo, you know?
Is that because
it looks so much like a vagina?
Carla, there's people!
You know, forget it.
- OK.
- Hit it.
Good, good. Your mom
re-did the bedroom again.
and I was riding
in an ambulance all night.
- I can't afford this place.
- Elliot, I'm $130,000 in debt.